Condition this day and age, a friendly face on every page.
A laugh track floating through the haze.
Everything feels safe these days.
The neighbor's wave, the children play.
The sun shines bright, the bills get paid.
The hands appear applauding.
OK, oh my gosh, right here.
Good morning.
Oh, let me fix it.
I was madder a little bit, I was a little bit more irritated a few minutes ago, but I just
ran to the store like three times, and so I lost a lot of steam on that.
But if I'm going to read you, I'll read you. I mean, read you like for filth. Some of you deserve it.
Some of you are cool people. Some of you are just chatters. Some of you are just like, you know,
just trolls, but some of you are just assholes. I mean...
Don't know. I mean it gets ridiculous not I mean it's like it and just take what applies to you
I mean this like if you're not I know you're not if you are you know you are you know, I mean it's like I
Mean one thing after another
No, I'll miss you. I'll miss you. I'm not going anywhere. I'll miss you. Oh, I'm not going anywhere
Oh, well, I am because you know, oh, I just wish you would have apologized to this person when I asked you
I think I did apologize to that person
You know it wasn't my fault
Hi, Rudy. Come here, Rudy. Rudy. Anyway, yeah, it's getting really dirty, especially like,
you know, bringing people's dead relatives into things. And so anyway, what else is new?
What else happened? My brand is being a dick again. I mean, it's like, that was my mistake.
If you're pretending you're, let's say, Kate's a turtle, right, and if someone comes in your chat, you have no idea about the backstory, really.
And then even the whole chat is saying, oh, don't have the person.
But then the people that, you know, go to her are Bita and Saman with evidence.
You know, maybe be a little bit stubborn, so maybe that maybe I'll be the same way
I don't know. That's just an example. It's like just imagine that like oh wait, so you're gonna just take your enemies
Worst for it. Well, they're trying to sabotage you anyway. They're trying to mess you up anyway
So it's like, you know if a friend comes to you
But then when your friends come to you and they're like, you know, he's not a horrible person actually
But they're scared of him, you know
Bet they even they can see some I don't know. I think there's probably is good in anybody
I think you know some of the stuff that has happened is like, you know, not good
but it's
You have to check the context of things you have to look at people's mental illness. Hi Rudy. Hi there you are
Hi, okay, I'm running up. Hi. Good morning. Good morning. Hello
Hi. Hi. What are you doing? Hi
You're very uh
Relately is very active and yeah, I don't I don't know. I don't think that
INX and with I mean, it's yes, it's
There's friendships. Oh, oh, you're there in love with each other. I mean, I guess people about this
Can't can't be friends. I mean, it's I gotta guess friendships can't change. It's okay for everyone else to I mean it's like but I mean
Geez, I mean there's so much with some some some people. It's it's crazy
Try try having a friend like a close friend
Unfriend you and re-friend you at least 30 times hang up on you when you're in the middle of a sentence
At least 10 times in a row
It gets crazy it gets so crazy it really does hi babe. Hi Lenore. You're there too
Give me your kiss. Oh, no, and then it's like, okay, let me get my I get my link up
So I want us to talk, but all right. Oh, you're giving me kisses. You're giving me kisses. Okay. We'll be kisses back
See, this is a very sweet guy. Hi wild German lady appears. How are you sweetheart?
Good to see you. Thank you for being here. I'll get you a mod if you were like one
Isn't this Lenore. Oh, you're giving me kisses. Oh, that's how you like it
Like your ear like that
Yep, she does yes sweetheart. Okay, here's me
Okay, I mean it's like I mean
When I go to for any do you take a walk? That's the good thing about taking walks
It's like, you know, I get to like kind of decide what I want to say
But then it's like I also lose a little steam of my anger a little bit
Because, you know, it is kind of like ridiculous. It's a certain point. I am not like a a mean person. I
Was nice. I mean, it's like I'm too nice. That's the thing. It's like he was nice. You control the month that
Someone's been like, oh, this person said this in your chat.
Oh, this person, do you understand?
That's a person saying it in my chat.
Like I really, I don't even like to please the chat.
Then if I do please the chat, oh my God,
they're deleting comments, they're deleting comments,
oh my God.
I mean, it's like a big up for it.
Everyone else can just see me to the side.
What's up, ghost or debater?
Everyone else can seem to decide what they want to do,
but it's like, it's always a problem
when I do what I want to do.
It's like, and I'm boycotted, I'm a terrible person.
I'm like, oh, just go, you know, bother him
and say terrible things to him in his chat, you know.
I'm on camera.
Literally, I was on Money 420s.
Literally, there's 10 or nine people on the panel.
I was the one person with the camera on,
like the one Money 420s panel.
Not one person had the camera on except for me.
And I just, I was like, okay, I knew Kristine was there.
So I was like, I was like, I'm just gonna let Kristine.
say whatever. What is the extortion crime? Brandon said, oh, well, you know, for my internship,
for his internship, he wanted $1,000 instead of like, you know, $300 or something, whatever
dollars. So that was part one of the extortion. Now part two of the extortion is he started
going around saying, oh, pay Psyche $2,000, which I never asked to say, I don't endorse.
And I said, don't say that because I don't want to be to making demands and all that
kind of stuff.
Um, and then I'll just be accused of trying to extort or something like that cat room granny
Well, who's the chat room granny love? I don't know but uh
Oh, yes. Yeah, she's exaggerating everything. I mean, it's like, but then she got really nasty. Oh, well, no wonder, you know,
you know, his father died. His father didn't leave him anything, but
Bitch, you don't know anything about it. Okay, and don't don't don't mean to get into what you got left out
You know, you don't want me to do that because that gets too personal
So it's like it really nasty of you that to have done that, you know, really a bitch move
You know, you can say anything you want. Don't call me PDF with my legal name next to it with no evidence and no just accusations
It's pure smear. Don't and don't mention my family members. I never went after your I was
anything I said
Between what we who had shared with me was in a nice complimentary understanding way without trying to slander hurt feelings
Or or any of this you're no better than Christine. You're a bunch of yours. You're just these bitches
I mean, it's like you're wicked wicked bitches instead of which which is you're being bitches
I mean it's like who else would bring up people's families like that like all the time
Brandon's doing to you know better than Brandon like really
You're all pretty much this I mean those those people the same energy really. I mean, it's like
Almost like the same demon running their mind
It's a probably a gay male demon, which I know how to deal with
Okay, but uh, anyway
Yeah, so
What else did I post my link? Well, I'll chat with anybody and stuff and you know, and I'll have my you know
And just like yesterday, it's like, if there's a negotiation,
oh, you know, I don't want this person on, I'm on.
Well, all this can be worked out and stuff like that.
I might turn into a bitty more sometimes.
You know, I'm trying to be fair and trying not to be,
you know, taking advantage of situations at the same time.
It's like, you know, this is part of my livelihood,
you know, it's like, it's not always easy.
I'm trying to raise cats, I'm trying to buy equipment for my show, run a show.
Have content and interesting things and upgrade things and and doing it without being monetized and doing it
Just under attack and doing it with like, you know, people actively saying oh, don't don't support him
Don't do this. Just go there and bother him and stuff like that. Do I do that?
I mean, I yeah, maybe I've gone and I've trolled in some rooms before maybe lately
I've been under all my alts when I keep getting hidden and stuff and I I've said stuff in reaction to the things that are said
But I never went
For no reason anywhere and started attacking people. It's always been
And I have a part of myself that's defensive that is like not even like
I'm not even like a hundred percent conscious of it's just a defender part of my personality
It's like if you're into astrology, it's Mars in the first house
in Aquarius
which is like
A very detached but but martial
personality
Whereas, you know, I feel like I'm finding a war sometimes and I'm in battle mode, you know
And I will defend myself because I do have like this like yeah, but there's chat room grannies around like you know, Christine
I mean, I mean just he's just awful and I just didn't like yesterday when I go into a chat room and I'm joking
Towards other people and then she has to type in the chat. Oh, you're a PDF supporter
You would be support hurting children and women and animals. You're I mean and then they put that on the screen
And then when I say, okay, well, you killed kids,
my comment gets deleted.
But they put hers on the screen about me.
They're both slanderous.
They're both untrue.
They're both ridiculous in a certain way, right?
But why is it like, oh, let's put Christine's up on the screen.
Oh, and then let's yell at Psyche,
because he's bad, because he's reacting to what she said.
I wouldn't have just come in there and said it.
But certainly I'll say it
if she makes it some kind of slanderous accusation towards me.
I'll say something ridiculous
They don't like it. I need to shut the fuck up about me. I don't I don't what is my doxing history
It's what I showed a picture. I should all I've ever done is shown pictures that are publicly available of
People that like, you know have problems my parents, but then they they keep putting Christine's comments on this
Yeah, I know they kept putting them on the screen. I I guys update and then that no matter how horrible they are
It's slanderous, horrible.
I'm sitting there joking about, you know,
sucking Harry Xionicus's dick.
And then all of a sudden,
I have to hear about PDF protector
and stuff like that again on the screen.
I mean, ridiculous.
Get it together, some of you.
I mean, it's like, you know, I, I mean,
that was like a rookie move that I did.
Like when I started, like, I would be like,
oh, here's all the comment on the screen,
I'm super chat.
And then it would be like some kind of, you know,
terrible thing about somebody.
I'm like, well, I don't really don't want to even
have to read that on the screen.
I mean, it's like, right?
It's like fight your own some people need to fight their own battles and stuff like that. You can fight him in the chat
I don't really care if people say in the chat. I don't know. I don't even have hardly anyone blocked except for you know
Allied which is like, you know, he's probably on Alts and I mean, it's like it's impossible. He has at least 50 alts of
Aiden
You know, and we have black RG is on a million. I mean, it's like
And then it is common and it seems like they're like a thing, but it's just like the same like loud like three people
Under a million alts called sock puppets accounts or whatever just bitching at me. I mean it's like terrible
It's terrible. It's really is terrible. I can't I'm gonna deal with some and then the people that are my friends
Oh, you think, oh, okay. Well, thank God. He has someone to go
They act such as they act just as bad sometimes. I mean, it's like or even worse. I mean, it's like, oh, well
And it's like, well, he's oh my god. I'm going through all this. Oh, well this and this about me
Well, I'm a little bit busy right now with like a thousand other people that are a man
You can you can you take a number rate of life? Yeah, she Christine is this know-it-all. She's miss
She's like, what does she think this is like some Southern beauty pageant or something and she's miss watermelon
you know, you know, 2026. I don't know. I don't know. She thinks she's like some kind of like
community treasure. I mean, Alexandra is a community treasure just because she's so insane
and she's so she's funny sometimes. Christine's not a community treasure. She's like she's like the
garbage by the side of the road. I mean, it's like, it's like, oh, you know, please free. Take a free,
my free couch with a big stain on it. That's what Christine is.
I mean, at least Alexandra's funny.
Kristine's not funny.
She's just like, you know,
I'd rather talk to my grandma, you know,
who passed away about how to make, you know, bread for hours.
Listen to Kristine, oh, I think she's still telling
her Easter egg hunt story.
I, yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, it's like,
she's perfect, I guess.
She's a perfect person.
You know, I was like, there's so many people
that are so perfect.
I mean, if you saw some of these people,
You know, I didn't know Bita looked like, you know, an ogreous and Samman looked like, you know, Cresty the Clown's cousin and stuff.
I mean, I didn't know that. I mean, they their pictures are so cute on there. I'm actually on camera. I don't even I don't have my fucking filter on right now.
I mean, it's like, oh, I look old and stuff like that. Have you seen these people? These people are criticizing how I look.
Have you seen some of these people? There's a reason they're called faces for radio.
I regret I even saw their real faces sometimes.
I mean, nightmares.
I mean, geez, Bakelips has it right.
I mean, with how they look.
I mean, you think he's making caricatures.
Well, the ones he would do to me are caricatures.
The one would be, is a praying mantis.
That's like a photo-realistic image of her.
I mean, she does the same thing.
She bites her, you know, the heads off of her,
her sexual partners.
She, I think her vagina has teeth.
I mean, is she wearing, I don't know if she wears a wig
or something like that, but I mean, geez, Vita.
You know, persons are supposed to have nice big,
that's why she got so mad.
Oh my God, when I did that picture of her.
Oh my God, she's like, look, that woman has hair.
Vita's like, that doesn't look like me.
You know, Vita's like, I have like a couple strands
that I comb over on the front.
Like honestly, I mean, and really, I mean,
if you've seen this woman, oh, they're criticizing me.
I'm so terrible.
I'm so, I mean, I'm awful, right?
Oh, it's hard.
I mean, it's like, and then it's like,
then I have friends, and then my friends all turn on me
at the same time as everyone else.
I'm like, well, you're supposed to help me right now,
not like pile on.
I mean, it's like, geez, it's hard.
It's hard, so I'm not gonna put my link again.
It's hard.
Hi, Vanette.
Yeah, hi, Lava.
Hi, Nancy.
Hi, guys.
Thanks for being here.
I mean, it's like, there's so many cool people in the chat.
Like I'm like, you know what I'm like, oh, I'm almost like, oh, I'm happy
Like about 90% of the people that aren't here. I'm happy. They're not here. I'm like, I've been waiting for them to get rid of them
Thank you, but yeah, I will I say everyone else is scared
Everyone else gets scared about it. They're intimidated. They want to be in them for that's okay
I'll be I'll be willing to be alone. You know, it's like I've been how I mean, I've been alone a lot
But I you know, I do have to say
For all the for all the all the problems. I'm I'm not doing bad on YouTube
I I think especially in this community that she's like does not know how to get a shit together to monetize
I've monetized pretty well. I'm proud of how that how I've done, you know
It's like I'm not worth it. Oh, I'm not here for them. I'm not here for the money and stuff
I'm just here for the fun. What fun is this if I wasn't getting paid. I wouldn't go through to put myself through this bullshit
I mean, it's terrible
What are these people doing here for free?
What are they, suckers for punishment?
I mean, honestly, I'm actually doing better financially
on YouTube now that I am and I'm monetized.
I've gotten more donations.
I promise to you, it's probably the only person
that's made more on YouTube in this community.
I would say probably Pebs and Zaya and KK.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm honest. Oh, and they they're oh, we don't care
Well, well good. That's you. I mean, they don't care. I mean, it's fine. I don't care
Why why am I evil because I'm trying to like feed myself. Yeah. Thank you for coming in that, you know, it's like
Oh, there's something wrong with making money and then it's like you then you don't have money
Oh my god, you're poor, you know, it's like you can't do anything right sometimes, right?
So I'm just gonna do myself. I'm just gonna
I don't care if I come off like,
oh, I mean, grifter is the furthest thing from it.
I provided services.
I've had people call me grifter
and then donate after that.
And so it's like, if they really think that,
it's, I mean, it's this flavor of the month, right?
It's just like, oh, they're happy.
I don't know if I'm dealing with them,
some extreme levels of bipolar personality disorder,
multiple personality disorder.
I think we need some lithium.
I mean, it's like everyone just take some lithium
and chill out.
Yeah, I wanna get back on the bike.
I mean, I do need to like, you know,
maybe like be able to make $20,
I can hold on for 10 minutes.
I can buy the stupid part.
I mean, it's like, I got one thing after another
to I'm trying to, you know, pay for.
It's not easy.
I mean, geez, thank you.
Are you enjoying this?
Okay, so that was my like,
not being a little ranch, but yeah.
So I don't know I think I might do some horoscopes today
It's the first of the month. I'm July 1st 7-1
7-1 is actually the
My unbirth day because I'm born 1-7. So this is the exact opposite number
Okay, so yeah, I mean I've got some interesting stuff to talk about and stuff
But I need someone to come up on panel Nick who wants to come up anybody want to come up?
You know, and then Christine that horrible Christine
Paid to kick Nancy out of the chat of money for 20 and Bronzeberg. Oh, yeah, so I was gonna tell the story
I went to her to to to money for 20. Oh, here comes cycle. Oh, okay, so I go in
There's Christine. I go and I just come quiet. I'm just I sit there
Listen, she goes off for a minute. Oh, you better protect her
You know, I'm just there, and she's like,
and I got rid of Nancy.
And I was like, who, reality Nancy?
Like why would you do that?
And then all of a sudden, summer.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, money, check your cash app,
check your cash app, oh, oh, Christine, oh, oh, oh.
Bye.
Yeah, we're welcome for making you $25 money might as well. Maybe sometimes say thank you to the person
I mean, I would say thank you personally behind the scenes
The people if I like to come on and say, you know, sorry, I say, it's like it's just business business
Looking at the president is Trump. I mean, it's like business of business sometimes, right? I try to keep it looking either. Yeah
I mean, it's like, if you don't make content, it's like, you know,
I mean, then have respect for content creators and stuff.
I mean, that's what, like, you know, a lot of these people don't make content.
They just use other people's, especially like mine, you know, and I will play.
I'll clip some stuff.
But yeah, and you take your money to bought for 24 hours for what in the chat?
I mean, are they like dumb?
Do they know that?
Like reality Nancy, if she really wanted to.
Could come back and in 10 seconds another name like you know happy
You know happy happy Gilmore or something and say whatever she wants and no one will even know the difference unless she says
Oh, it's me. It's Nancy. You know how how hard it is to
To block somebody from a chat. I'm a ridiculous that I post link again
Say when I come up here. I mean I
Feel so bad for sick sick hurt is his mouth or something
Thought it was a joke like I like someone put a picture up on in my discord of sig and I was like oh look at sig
I was like why is he making that terrible face?
You ever hear like oh, don't make that face or it will get stuck like that
Well, sick learn that the hard way. Oh, well, I'm sorry
Sick had to learn that listen the hard way look what happened to him. That's what he that's his normal face now
It's not a joke. I mean, I wish it was. I feel bad for him. I think he might have had a stroke or something
Yeah, that's what he looks like now though. His mouth is all like exploded
He's like this
He then he hit and then he puts his camera on like like that. So he like goes like this and it's really frightening thing
Yeah, I know it's like it's not even worth it going fake alts and stuff like that. And then they have oh, oh, I'm a person
You know if I could get my mods to do anything my mods will barely even block anybody
You know for me, maybe but it's like oh everyone else. Oh, you know beat it
It's like I'm saying that she has like a bodyguard system. It's like, you know, yeah
He looks like Jason Momoa got you know kid in the face with them with the rugby ball or something
That's what he looks like now.
Sig, I'm sorry.
It's like a tragedy.
It was hard enough for him to get laid before.
Imagine now.
Imagine if you go on Grindr or Tinder
and this guy shows up at the restaurant.
I'm sorry, Sig.
I feel so bad for you.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you, Rose Regis.
Well, you don't have to block me.
Just like time people out for 10 seconds.
If they're like terrible, you know,
I mean, you get when people are terrible.
I'm a little bit staggy.
I'm sorry, SIG.
I should animate that picture.
I think I'm gonna animate that picture.
Maybe I can like animate it into like, you know,
give him some ideas on how to, um, maybe like,
cause some, maybe SIG, maybe if you like, you can like,
you know how your face is stuck like that?
Maybe you can like try to do another face
and it won't look like that anymore.
I know it's hard.
I'm so sorry.
How'd that happen?
And look at Bita. Look at this woman. Oh shit, hold on.
This is what Bita looks like if she was merged with Sandman.
That's what they would look like. Now imagine that.
That's even worse than the clumsy picture.
That's Sandman with Bita's nose and hair.
I mean, talk about the scary.
Jeez.
And I'm ugly, right?
I'm like the ugliest, you know, or I'm the, I don't know.
I don't like being called a low cow by like low cows.
I mean, it irritates me because you can tell me
a lot of things.
I'm like, I don't like, I don't want to be called a cow
by literally heifers.
They're literally heifers.
And look at this.
Imagine you go, you go, you go to a date on Grindr.
And he made it like this Latino guy, right?
And he'd think, oh, he's a bald Latino guy.
He's gonna be good looking and stuff.
And what the fuck is a little cow?
I don't know.
But look, and then he shows up.
You wanna make, you wanna eat clumsy
and he shows up with a bald gag in his mouth.
I look like a scuffed, Casey Nista.
Well, Sig, I mean, it's a little bit,
that's a little bit obscure of a reference.
I don't know who Casey Neistat is, first of all.
Second of all, I mean, it's like,
high, inner beauty shines strong.
It does, look at my, look.
And I'm like, I'm like this, what, this addicted meth head.
You know, I look like I'm 75 years old.
I know I have a little bit of gray in my beard.
I'm 45 years old.
I'm not like a spring chicken anymore,
but I'm not like an old, an old, you know,
cow ready to be shot in the pasture like Christine.
I mean, jeez, how dare she?
This woman is 75 years old saying, I look old.
This woman, I mean, look what she does.
Oh, here's my picture.
This is a picture she literally put out
as her own picture, okay?
You would think it's Christine Turlington
at some kind of beach photo shoot.
Oh, look at this sexy, this woman is incredibly beautiful
and gorgeous.
Oh, it's just an AI photo of Christine.
I mean, talk about AI.
Oh, psychic is AI.
I mean, okay, yeah, let's talk about me and my AI.
Look what she did to herself.
I mean, literally, look at the picture she puts out of herself.
I mean, geez, talk about AI.
Good Lord.
Now I got branded.
I'm branded to frog.
I don't care what you frog.
Oh, gamble, gamble, gamble.
Oh my God, who cares?
Just go fuck him already. I mean jeez. I mean you guys
The fuck
You got muted you're not even on the air
It's impossible to mute you. Oh, then Alex McQueen. Look at Alex McQueen. He hasn't been back here for months. Oh
He asked me for McDonald's
They cop bitch. You're not a cop. You're some kind of
Cocaine dealer or something. I don't I don't even know
Bro, I don't know, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, it's like if my bro is Kermit the frog
I know I like Alex McQueen too, but he's he's he's he's
He said oh, I'm forcing him to buy me McDonald's
How stupid how how horrible does that make me look? I'm extorting. I might I'd rather be extorting Ronald McDonald
And then you know Alex McQueen. I mean at least and then I have like a you know
Let's a little bit less of a clown to deal with
Geez I know I know I'm going to I'm going too far. So I'm going too far. I'm so sorry. I
Know I don't want to roast everybody
But geez, I mean people have been so mean to me. Oh, we have a guest. Oh, I'm in trouble
Hold on a second. Interesting guys
Who's your man? Oh, he's gonna call me loser. Oh, I'm a loser. Oh
Brandon Brandon Brandon
Don't make me do it. Don't make me do it. Oh
You don't mean to go through all the all the videos and I mean, it's like no, I'm not don't make me do it
If you keep docking my family members names, I will and we will definitely do a deep dive into all of this
I mean Alexander's already contacted your you know, you're illegal immigrant, you know escorts, you know, it's working on
No legal paperwork right now as we speak so don't push it with me. Oh, who's saying I hurt my cats
I hurt my cat. Well, I don't know. I want him to get into, I want him to get into, you know, yeah, a little bit immature.
I mean, Brandon, you're telling INX this nice lady that, I mean, all we ever do is be nice to you.
Oh, you're lying. You're stupid. Oh, talk about Carissa being a rapist. And I mean, it's just like, I mean, it's like, but no, not, no, not anymore.
Not anymore. I might have been attracted to his massive kids at first, but no. I can just look at Isaiah.
I was looking at Isaiah.
He was hating on me with him like 10, 15 minutes ago.
INX was hating on me with him.
Oh my God.
INX, what happened?
She called me weird and said I hurt my cats too.
Oh my God, I need to talk to her.
But your name is Ice Smoke Meth.
And so I don't know if I trust you.
Oh, is he like a viper?
I mean, this is the story.
This is the story.
I mean, I have the story.
This is like, you know, this will describe Alexandra.
This will describe Brandon Q.
This is the story.
I don't know if you guys have heard this, but
beautiful story.
This is the great Donald Trump told the story.
You wanna hear it?
However you do.
Okay.
Oh, we know I don't.
My cats wouldn't be here if they were.
Cats don't stick around, right?
I smoke meth as a reputable source in the community.
Okay, well, here we go.
Do we see this on the screen?
This is how I feel after taking in Alexandra
and Brandon and stuff here.
This is how I feel.
What's happening is so different.
Kamala is so radical.
She even wants to legalize fentanyl.
She wants fentanyl coming.
When one little drop can destroy you,
which is pouring, it's pouring across our.
Borders at record levels at levels that you've never seen before fentanyl have how many people I mean everybody
I know they have family members that are dying mostly
children what
They have something else where it's something that and it's laced with fentanyl and they end up dying a vicious death by the way
What you know, I brought something to snake does anybody want to hear we don't have to do it if you want to get back
Should we do the snake or not?
Should we do it?
It's so apropos, right?
250 and he wants to eat the snake, but it's true.
It's just so bad.
But it is apropos, isn't it?
So for those of you who has not heard the snake?
Who has heard the snake?
And they don't care, they want to hear it again.
Let's do it. This is about the border, essentially. It was an old song and
little rewording and things but it was a very very apropos and I think
I think very good in a lot of ways gotta learn your lesson on her way to work one morning
Down the path along the lake a tender-hearted woman saw her poor half-rozen snake
His pretty colored skin had been all frosted with the dew.
Poor thing, she cried, I'll take you in and I'll take care of you.
Take me an otender woman, take me in for heaven's sake.
Take me an otender woman inside the vicious snake.
She wrapped him up all cozy in a comforter of silk and
laid him by her fireside with some honey.
and some milk. She hurried home from work that night, and soon as she arrived, she found the pretty snake she'd taken in had been revived.
Take me in, O'Tender Woman. Take me in for heaven's sake. Take me in, O'Tender Woman, beside the vicious snake.
She touched him to her bosom. You're so beautiful, she cried.
But if I hadn't brought you in by now, you truly would have died.
She stroked his pretty skin again and kissed and held him tight.
But instead of saying, thank you, ma'am, the snake gave her a vicious bite.
Take me in, Oten to woman, take me in for heaven's sake.
Take me in, Oten to woman, inside the vicious snake.
I saved you, cried the woman, and you've bitten me.
But why you know your bite is poisonous.
And now I'm going to die.
Shut up, silly woman, said the reptile with a grin.
You knew damn well I was a snake before you took me in.
That's what's happening when I'm born.
that's what's happening on our border i mean we can get a phd and whatever it is from the best
school in the world is not going to be more accurate than that let's do some fun with animations
okay okay we're gonna do some fun with animation just give me a few minutes
very back hi it's my l i don't care who smokes meth i don't really care i mean it's like whatever
We gather in the dark at half past 3 a.m. Performing ancient rituals for seven viewers
and a cat named Rudy Hymn.
At the sacred tarot, the nine of Pentacles reversed Which means some things upside down
are possibly a curse.
The cult of psyche rises, we got lore and we've got vibes
We got four copyright strikes and nobody to ride
Later's asleep but the show goes on
Someone in the chat said, fish chocolate
Hail psyche we think, mostly show up but sometimes we drink
The terraces our futures are unclear
So does the nine up right?
So does the nine reverse my day?
I had to summon a sadder fear
In spite of reversed
Which means someone spilled their men
The coat of psyche gathered on a
They said I was obsessed
While streaming about me for three hours
They said I needed help
While burning candles and rolling something at 8 a.m.
They said leave us alone
Right after they named their spider ritual after me
Pulled a card about this
It was the fool
Which is very on brand
The odds the old ricks has knocked it down
Didn't care, almost ready
We said that about last June
Hail Psyche, rethink
Or as deep the coffees gave
The terror it says today
There's two, it's probably you
The can be reversed tomorrow are you for some fun now? Let's have some fun. Okay
I like to call this little routine of the oracle shield is a liability waiver. Okay
Okay, so I did something a little bit deranged this week
I built a searchable AI powered fully indexed database of every word
I have ever said on the stream
2,770 episodes
3,035 hours
4.7 million transcript segments and instead of using it to defend myself in an argument like a normal narcissist
I use it to write a comedy set
with that. I built a surveillance state of myself for content and chat and here's
the part that should worry you I didn't even have to make anything up. I just ran
a query. This entire set is sourced. This is the most well-researched thing I
have ever said out loud and it's about to be biscuits and a cat. We're gonna start
with the numbers.
because the numbers already know something none of you
are ready to hear.
So, codex.me, that's the archive.
So, go donate and it has, as of this taping, 2,770 episodes, 1,247 people documented, 8,501 lore entries, 3,521 quotes, 3,520 lore entries, and lexicon, and I know you said most of them, it's me by so much.
2000 of the quotes are me talking, that's 78%.
78% of the recorded wisdom of this entire civilization
is one man, hunched over a webcam at 1 a.m.,
talking about his own feelings.
And you people archived it,
like it was the Dead Sea Scrolls.
So second place is the unknown, quote,
210 quotes attributed to the speaker
that the AI genuinely could not identify.
So some of you have said less than a ghost.
The ghost is outperforming you.
So third place in the quotes,
and I want you to really absorb this.
Third place with 76 quotes is Tricks,
my cat, born on Pi Day.
A cat has more recorded quotable dialogue in this archive
than every single guest who has ever sat on this panel,
except for one.
You've come on the show. You poured your heart out. You cried on the camera. You've exposed your whole family's trauma for
content and my cat who contributes nothing but ambient noise and a
Paw occasionally entering frame is beating you on the leaderboard of things psyche as said that's not a stat
That's a diagnosis
And here's my favorite one, the Lore, 8,501 entries, 77 of its marked canonical.
That means somehow, somewhere, somebody sat down.
formally certified 77% of the insane things that have happened on this
stream. As real, official, agreed-upon history, 17% is speculative, only 1%
58 entries is disputed. 58 out of 8,500 only 58 things that I have that have
ever happened in this cult are considered upper debate. Okay. Everything else we
like a jury that's been locked in a room since 2024
and started hallucinating a legal system
and the topic breakdown,
because we tag every episode by the subject right now.
Apparently, tarot readings, 315 episodes, personal growth, 300 episodes, community drama,
178 relationships, 150 cats, 130, spirituality, 123, astrology, 113, cats outrank the astrology
chat.
On a show about the mystical forces governing the human destiny, the cats are statistically
more load-bearing than the planets.
Saturn's out here doing generational trauma work
in 11 year cycles,
and Trix walked across the keyboard one time
and got a whole category.
So then we have the leaderboard.
So speaking of hallucinated legal systems,
we have a leaderboard now.
The ascendant leaderboard ranked by contribution,
collection, and time in the cult.
You are in badges.
There's a rank called initiate.
There's a rank called addict.
It's a webcam panel discussion show that has invented a caste system.
You want to know who's number one?
Me.
I'm number one on my own leaderboard.
The title, Coat Leader Badge, ADAPT 65 points.
I built the game and I wrote the scoring system and then I checked and shockingly I win.
Nobody tell the Olympic committee that I've also been quietly refereeing my own events.
Number two chat. This one's real number two on the leaderboard of most devoted human beings in this community
57 points
Title oracle is an account called IP to wiki info. That's not a person
That's a wippy well wiki scraping bot a bot is more committed to this cult than you are
It is never watched an episode. It is never laughed at a joke
It doesn't have feelings to hurt or life to neglect and it is still out here outworshipping
actual human beings with jobs and children in student loans.
So if a bot can rank Oracle tier by doing literally nothing but existing near my content,
what does that say about the effort required to beat it?
in the right direction.
Number three is a human.
Congratulations, Reality Nancy.
54 points, you beat a robot by three.
And I want you to know that it is genuinely
most impressive thing anyone has accomplished
on the stream all year.
So we already established Triggs has 76 quotes.
Let's talk about Lenore for a second,
because Lenore's entry in the lexicon,
and I did not write this.
The fans wrote this, calls her quote,
OG familiar, an unofficial cult mascot.
Familiar, as in witchcraft.
My cat has a job title in a cult hierarchy
that outranks half the people who've been on this panel.
There are guests who've done six episodes and don't have a lexicon entry.
Lenore sleeps 18 hours a day and gets familiar.
And on the archive, on my own profile, this one really got me.
I'm described, and again, community-written, not mine as father of cats and speaker of
the void.
bio and more like something engraved on a tombstone.
Nobody wanted to visit.
Nine cats.
I've had nine cats co-hosting a live stream
about astrology and betrayal.
So if NASA had this many redundant systems monitoring
a single mission, we'd have colonized Mars twice by now.
Instead, we have nine cats making sure nobody on this stream
Feels too stable for too long
So let's talk about how justice works around here in the ban economy because I looked it up
And I want somebody to explain the ethics of this to me. There is a documented
lexicon entry official policy for $25
You can buy a 24-hour ban on yourself
Or with a shorter dollar per minute rate if you'd like something more
Boutique. We have invented pay-per-view incarceration. You can purchase your own time-out. Somewhere
in this community, there is a person who, in a moment of chat-induced rage, opened their
banking app and thought, you know, what would fix this feeling? Jail. But I choose the link
That's not a ban system. That's a wellness retreat with worse branding and then then there's a flip side
mass unban a documented
recurring event
Where I periodically wipe the entire ban list and invite every single
Enemy this community has ever made back into the building all of them at once
on purpose
So the actual justice system of this cult is
You can pay to go to jail voluntarily, and then on a schedule that nobody controls, the warden, me,
just opens every cell at the same time because he missed the drama.
This is not a moderation policy. This is a full lunar cycle. We are the only community on the internet.
running restorative justice and a revenge arc
on the same calendar.
And the lexicon has a term, the Switzerland philosophy.
My stated neutrality in community drama, neutral.
I am the neutral party who personally controls
the ban button, personally controls the unban button.
And personally ranks number one
on the leaderboard of devotion to myself.
That's not Switzerland
Switzerland doesn't own their bank
But maybe they should you know, we do have a friend from Switzerland and she's great. Her name is
They don't remember her name. Oh, I remember her name and her name is um
Gosh darn it. Oh, I'm James Bond. Her name is James Bond, right?
Okay, so are you I hope you're enjoying this because we're about halfway through, you know
But I want you to really think about these things because, you know, I put a lot of work into this cult
You know, and it's like, I don't know. I don't know if my work is always appreciated, you know
So I digress, you know, and thank you reality Nancy. Thank you
You know the robot at ip2wiki.info
You guys are superstars, but
So am I right?
Okay, so
So real quick, because we have 450 entries in the community glossary, and I need you
to understand how far gone we are.
These are all real, all currently live on the site right now.
So we have ogling.
That means creepily.
Oggling someone on camera. We needed a word for that. Oggling. We also built one. Pluh.
And I want to read the actual definition of pluh. Nonsense interjection used as filler or chaos energy.
Pluh. We catalog sound. A grunt has an entry. A grunt is more precisely defined in this glossary.
than most state constitution.
So we have the term zitty,
a term of endearment for loyal viewers.
It sounds like a Pixar sidekick.
It's you, that's you, people, zitties, okay.
The girls are fighting, chat phrase use,
and I'm quoting the site,
when two panelists bicker regardless of gender.
We built a gender neutral idiom for chaos.
That's actually kind of progressive, ironically.
On a show also that has an entry called
Ogling, and my personal favorite, panel archaeology, digging through old episodes to surface forgotten
lore.
You're not rewatching content.
You're not catching up.
You are conducting a dig.
Somewhere out there, one of you has a trowel and a brush, gently excavating my worst 3AM
take from October, like it's a dinosaur bone.
450 terms. We have more slang than some languages. One more round faster, because chat asked
for it and I'm contractually obligated to give the chat what it wants. That's a documented
lexicon entry too. It's called chat speed. Flying monkey. Someone manipulated into doing
We have gray rock. It's becoming so deliberately boring. So a toxic person loses interest in you
Which if you think about it is just what I've been doing
To the IRS so we have MPC someone repeating opinions on autopilot. We have the Lulu
believing something can be clearly untrue, especially about relationships.
We have cooked. That means utterly destroyed in an argument.
We have gonged. That's the removal from the panel abruptly named after the gong show.
We have caught in 4k. That is undeniable evidence. We have simp. We have riz. We have sus.
That's 10 more definitions in under 30 seconds and every single one of them
was coined to describe behavior happening.
this channel in real time by people who are currently watching me read their own
vocabulary back to them. So next we get the biscuit gate and the cannon, okay?
Biscuit gate. I need everyone to understand. This is an official cataloged
lexicon entry piece of history now. So I quote, months-long feud between Psyche
and Vita starting over biscuits torment.
There was, apparently, an entire AI-generated diss track produced during this war, using,
and I need you to hear this phrase again, biscuit metaphors to call out shallowness.
Months.
A biscuit-based Cold War lasted months.
There are actual geopolitical conflicts that resolved faster than Biscuit Gate.
Somewhere, a foreign policy analyst is studying the Camp David records, and I'm telling you
that a beef about pastries in my chat outlasts it, and the thing is the archive doesn't editorialize.
It doesn't go in, that was silly.
It just files it right there next to 12th House Venus and Hindu Tantric Goddess entries
filed with total institutional seriousness is a war about biscuits.
Same weight, same tone, same 77% canonical certification.
That's the real joke buried in this whole database.
The astrology is canon. The biscuits are canon. My extortion situation. And yes, that's a real quote from me on the record, quote,
I don't know why my name is on some kind of extortion. It's like, no, no, no, no, no, no. And that's canon too.
Somewhere in this archive, a genuine federal adjacent crime allegation and a pastry beef are sitting in the same database.
Formatted identically both flag 77% likely to be real because to this community
There is no difference in magnitude
between
someone trying to extort me and
Someone called my biscuits shallow
It's all just Tuesday
So next we have the oracle shield now the lexicon has an entry called the oracle shield
So official definition quote
the moment Alexandra Mayer's defended psyche against coordinated attacks.
She has her own show on this network now,
Alexandra Mayer's real recurring guest, real archived quotes,
and I want to walk you through the actual transcript,
because the co-host breakdown of how a smear campaign works is genuinely
Organize crime lecture that I have ever accidentally filmed.
Direct quote on the record.
If an instigator can successfully coerce you into lying for them,
they have effectively compromised you.
You now share a dirty secret.
Another one.
You have dirty information,
a lie or smear generated by an unreliable source
to get the community to buy it.
you have to run it through a clean enterprise.
And then, breaking down a specific incident,
when Amber asked Alexander to lie about Gainville,
she was plucking the thread.
She was testing the tension
of Alexandra's moral boundaries.
Chat, that is not gossip.
That is a trade-craft briefing.
Somebody on this panel can explain reputation laundering
with more precision than most cable news legal analysts.
And she's doing it between a tarot poll
and a cat walking through the frame.
And then, because the show does not know
how to stay in one register for longer than 90 seconds,
Alexandra also delivered some, the same season, a quote,
I do love you very much, and if you betray me
or anyone else I care about, I will destroy you.
And 20 minutes later, on the same stream, quote,
My loneliness is killing me.
That's the whole arc, the threat of annihilation
to open vulnerability in under.
30 minutes, if a therapist saw that shift in session notes, they would schedule an emergency
follow-up.
But we put it on YouTube with a thumbnail.
Okay, so let's talk about the staff, the mods.
Because I have a moderation team, and I want to read you their actual archived job descriptions.
Quote,
AC is a power mod on my channel,
which who helps to manage the chat AC a long time ago.
That's it, that's the whole entry.
Somewhere there's a guy with actual real world authority
over hundreds of people's ability to type.
And his entire biography is one sentence.
Long like a hostage proof of life photo. So Alexander McQueen. That's a mod on this channel
Alexander McQueen
the dead British fashion designers name currently deployed
Keeping order in a chat that also has an entry for porn bomb
31 appearances, I don't know if he knows I don't know if I knew when I let it happen and then
And this is a real documented person on the site, 300 glow, bio direct quote, a guest
who pointed a gun at the camera during the show.
That's it.
That's his whole resume.
No follow-up, no incident report.
Just filed.
Canon. New entry. We have a more rigorous vetting process for who gets a blue checkmark than we do for who gets
handed a live microphone on this channel. And the appearance counts don't help my case.
I've appeared on my own show 1,253 times, which, fine, it's my show.
But after me, the most frequent guest is Jamie's Cowboys at 107 appearances, beaters
at 54.
These are people who've shown up to the stream more times than most people go on to therapy.
And unlike therapy, nobody's tracking whether it's working.
Okay, so we have the red room.
Now, for the people paying me,
because we have tiers on the website,
we have an Oracle tier.
Okay, we have members only section
that I call the red room,
and I want to read you the actual copy
from the login page,
because I did not write comedy this good on purpose.
So it says where the unfiltered analysis lives.
No diplomatic phrasing, no softening.
That's the sales pitch.
Pay me and I will stop being nice to you.
That's the premium tier.
Everywhere else on the internet you pay
for the deluxe, gentler experience.
Here, the free version is where I'm restrained.
You give me money and I get meaner.
This is the only subscription service
where loyalty is punished.
And I want every one of you oracle members to think about that the next time your card gets charged the tease red room episode titles real currently on the site.
Quote, whatever you do, don't fall asleep.
Quote, the internet's most dangerous digital circus.
Quote, welcome to my nightmare.
So those aren't episode titles.
Those are things a hostage says into a camera,
hoping someone recognizes the wallpaper behind him.
And you people are paying a monthly subscription for it.
So that brings me to the community and I have a diagnosis. Okay, so I want to stop roasting individuals for a second
and I want to roast the organism because
We don't just have lore. We have a documented
self-aware clinical vocabulary for how this community treats itself and
Reading it back is genuinely like getting your own group chats
Discharge papers
So we have a term community fracture audience splitting along fault lines during drama. We have click quote
exclusive group gatekeeping social
Access eroding others confidence. We have
Fairweather fan who is someone who only shows up when things are going well and vanishes the second there's controversy
We have parasocial collapse the exact moment of viewers one-sided imaginary friendship with me shatters on
Contact with reality. We have rent-free when someone occupies your thoughts without paying which
incredibly
Somebody wore a workshop landlord terminology into an insult about obsession and my favorite because it draws on a
actual moral line
The community apparently needed spelled out dog pile versus roast a roast
Per the glossary has affection underneath of it. That's what I'm doing right now
A dog pile is a crowd collectively attacking one person until they're buried and the entry specifically notes
It's distinct from roast by cruelty
Somebody had to write that distinction down
somebody looked at this group of adults and thought
Hmm, we should probably clarify for legal and emotional reasons the difference between
making fun of you and destroying you.
That footnote exists.
Right because of Christine, you know, basically Christine is trying to destroy me, right?
And we'll go into chats and say don't go into psyches chat. She'll say I am a
Protector of abusers and animal abusers and and I'm
basically the worst person in the world, right?
I mean, it's like, and so actually she kicked out,
reality of Nancy kicked out of the room yesterday
and paid for that, just get out of the chat room
because of reality of Nancy's association.
And so it's like, you know, people like Abita and Samman
and, you know, money for 20 start making money,
you know, off of you.
I mean, I think it's time for us need to like, you know,
consider
Consider the source because you know
While I will have a clapping system, you know, it'll be to my discretion if it's if something's
I mean, I usually I'll have to like not like the person either. But anyway, there's also panel purgatory
So we have the waiting room limbo between being invited on the show and actually getting let on the show and
Then we have hate watching
which is tuning in specifically because you dislike something,
and then complaining about it, right, live in the chat, you chose to be in.
That's not fandom.
Okay, that's just a poor group that meets nightly
uh-huh and
Refuses to stop meeting and then buried at the bottom
Almost tender backup joy a reserve of joy stored within the cults untouchable by trolls or
strikes so somewhere underneath the biscuits and
the extortion and the pay-to-be at band justice system
Somebody on this team wrote a definition for hope
and filed it alphabetically between
auto type and awakening.
That might be the most honest thing
in the entire 8,500 entries.
We built an encyclopedia for chaos
and accidentally left one entry for why we all stayed anyway.
So I want to go through the fine print real quick. Thank you for listening to my little spiel
I also want you to read the about page on the site because legally I think this matters quote on the about page
This is an independent fan project explicitly not an official publication
also a quote
Profiles describe on-stream performance and discussion not verified
real-world claims so the actual load-bearing legal defense of this entire archive
The thing standing between me and a subpoena is
None of this has to be true. We just have to have said it on camera. That's the whole architecture
So three channels cult of psyche psyche's nightmares
nightmare frequencies TV
The same guy wearing three different amounts of eyeliner
running what is functionally an unlicensed evening news broadcast for a
jurisdiction that doesn't exist. And the terms of service say, and I'm paraphrasing
slightly, please don't believe any of this in a court of law, that disclaimer
isn't a footnote. That disclaimer is the load-bearing wall of the entire
operation. And here's the one that actually got me.
There is a lexicon entry for our Sunday morning stream, official term, church of psyche awakens, definition, quote, Sunday morning streams, reframed as spiritual gathering, combining tarot and therapy.
We didn't call it a Sunday show, we called it church on purpose.
Consciously somebody typed that into a glossary with a straight face and the terrifying part is they weren't wrong. I
Get up early. I light a candle
I gather the flock, I dispense wisdom.
I'm not licensed to dispose.
The only difference is between me and an actual pastor
is I take donations instead of collection plate
through Cash App, cult of psyche,
dollar sign cult of psyche, and statistically better lighting.
So in the closing, okay, let's land on the plane
on the only way the show knows how.
I'm gonna do a reading on myself.
using the data.
Okay, so card one, the leader board,
rank one, quote leader, reversed.
The card usually means delusion of control.
Upright in this deck specifically,
it apparently just means accurate.
So card two, the quote archive, 78% self-authored.
In any other tradition, that's called a diary.
In this one, we called it community wisdom.
and put it behind a paywall.
Card three, tricks.
The cat outrinks the humans.
I used to think that was an insult.
Having sat with this data for a week,
I've changed my mind.
I think tricks is just the only one
who never had to perform to be believed.
Not a bad note and a show about authenticity
on even if the source is a cat.
who has never said a word and not been back in weeks.
And the last card, the one Lexicon calls the fool,
first card in the deck, new beginnings, blind faith,
stepping off a cliff without checking what's underneath.
I pulled that card on the stream and on the record
and said, and this is verbatim,
this is the actual archive quote,
That's a perfect one the first card. I don't know at that time
I was also describing the entire business model. So here's your benediction. So it's apparently
That's a documented part of how we close things around here. Go build something that audits you back
Something honest and up to catch you before it catches everyone else
Mine told me I'm outranked by a bot and a cat
And it was right both times and I'm still standing here 65 points cult leader adept badge
Absolutely delighted about it. Thank you for the biscuits
Thank you for the extortion. Thank you for ogling me
So I'll see you at the red room. No diplomatic phrasing. No softening
Thank you. Now, let me check the chat. Wow the chat's on fire. Hey KZ
I'm not stealing nor hoarding cats.
How do you think that is?
Did you like that?
Well, you have to go back and hear my whole set.
I just did a roast, basically of myself, but you know.
What's happening?
What do you think that is?
How are you?
Good to see you.
KZ, how are you?
I'm not stealing anybody's cats.
People have stolen my cats.
I did hope you enjoyed that though.
You heard it, okay, good.
What's happening?
What isn't happening?
mean I'm dealing with a bunch of insane people that that's first of all I mean
it's like the it just keeps getting worse and worse everyone keeps getting more
and more insane and eventually I'm gonna become insane you're okay don't stand
okay I'll make you I'll cheer you up look at this picture and look at this is
with if this is a beat in Sam and like became a head of child it would look
And then, this is what Sig looks like now
because his face got stuck this way.
Did I get a smile?
Oh yeah, and here's Christine's catfish photos.
Oh, you're looking for the link?
Okay, hold on.
Come on down!
You're the next contestant on my show.
I know, it is dealing with a bunch of bullies.
I mean, it's like, but they're...
I mean, they're just crazy.
I mean, it's like, it's just like,
I can't wrap my head around it sometimes.
Hey, my skin is looking pretty good lately though.
Look, I don't know if it's, I got these wipes.
They're these Birx Bees, like, I see.
I guess I can recommend them,
they're called these soothing wipes or whatever.
But I use them a few times and they,
my skin is like looking really good.
I do say so myself, so here.
You never say I'm, oh my God.
Brandon you call me you call me a loser and you're doxing me and stuff like and I've been so nice to you like what like what?
What oh, you're nice to me. Yeah
You're nice to me kicking on my panel and then having a gamble in your chat now. You have gamble modded fuck you, bro
Who's gonna nice?
You're a fake nice. Who's gonna stop banning that stop banning. That's gamble. You're dumb, bro
Oh, you've been so nice to me. You use me bro. You use me
You fucking use me, bro, but now enjoy it. Enjoy it, bro
You made your bed man. Fuck you, bro. Kicking me off because Karen said you're fake, bro
She said she didn't give you shit and even a fuck that's still you're sick, bro
Having gamble in the chat lie about me and shit. Oh, yeah, everybody go check out my new video
It's already going viral in one hour to one hour to go viral of gamble expose themselves
I'm using you. You're promoting on my show about this gamble person. Hey, but I've asked you who's who's gambling chat though?
Stop banning, please. Oh
Okay, well, I don't know how they're modded. I'll mod them. I mean, it's like I don't know. They don't have a great name
I thought I was shit, bro. You've already done the same shit three times. Well, you're a backstabber you're fake
You're a snake. You're the fucking snake, bro. The fuck calling me a snake. You're a fucking snake
I was calling Alex a snake, but you know, you're like that's a snake, bro
Call me a snake go call me a snake on your show. How are you gamble? You're a girl first of all
I know well
So Brandon is brand you're saying gamble has a vagina. That's what you're saying, Brandon
No one thinks it's gamble for Brandon. You're nuts. I mean, what is I'm using you am I over on your show?
You know yelling at you. I don't know. I think I just don't understand. It's like I
Thought stop banning was just big clips
Because I'm when I would whenever I ban big clips they would come on and say stop banning
So I was just like I thought it was just I could make mod big clips without modding big clips actually, you know
I mean they said stop banning. I assume they're not gonna start banning people their whole name is stop banning
So I assume it's like somebody to talk and be banning
unless they're just like really
I know. I was like, wow. I mean, I mean, I know I'm like, you know, I think we're all serpentine in some of them.
You're talking about snakes. Hey, babe. I think cats are like part snakes. Lenore has beautiful snake eyes.
Okay, I don't think it's gamble. I mean, it's like, what? Because it says Brandon smokes meth. I mean,
All I can say is there must be some kind of meth psychosis. I mean, it's like, how does everyone run some nuts?
Here you go. Come on. Let me go up. Let me go up on my shoulder.
Hey, okay. Hey
Okay, I come over here. What are you doing? You're thinking I'm gonna sit there. Okay. I have been night
I am a nice person. I was nice. I was I was nice old-time. I mean, I never called you stupid or any of these things
And like, you know, and I put up with a lot of like fucking abuse, you know, just, just like just saying, oh, hey, give the guy a chip, but you, but you act crazy. And I don't know. And it's like, I know I have questions about you because it's like, you know, I just thought you were joking before, but now you don't seem to have much of a sense of humor.
So it's like, maybe you weren't joking. And I mean, not even those things were funny, but it's like, I can understand if like some people just have sick jokes and stuff like that. But I don't know.
Wait, what? Now you think you're like Ionix's puppeteer. She has her own mind. She knows when people are using her and stuff. You weaponize her.
I can tell that, but eventually she'll figure that out, or maybe she just likes you and stuff like that, but I know about the elites and stuff like that.
Yeah, that was another thing. It's just a mess.
I mean you came in here taking up a lot like so much of like my day of the energy of the show and stuff like that
And then you're mad at me. I mean, it's like really it's like and then it's like, oh, why'd you kick me off if you donate?
Okay, like the other day. Yeah, you donate and thank you for that and stuff like that
I appreciate that but then you started like, you know calling me a loser and stuff and said I was sick and disgusting and
So I was like, okay, I don't feel like having you on the panel at this second, right?
And now it's like well because I like I re-modded you because it's like I just like trying to keep you trying to keep you like not
Deleted in the chat and stuff like that. Oh now now I'm extortionous because I'm you know and blah blah blah blah blah blah
Let's get so delusions psyche notices shit. He says he stalks and
Researched everyone then he keeps their info and pigs. I know he's I mean he's he's he's he's saying I'm a transgender
He I mean he's he's saying I'm a transgender named Judith or something like that. I mean, I mean, I don't understand
I mean, it has to be some kind of like, you know mental illness. I mean, it's like I'm not a transgender
Haven't you seen my bulge? I mean don't make me get out the speedo. Hi, babe
I know I know you're gonna come up and now you got you took the attention
What's wrong with my screen? I think I just have my uh, my
It's not a filter, it's my green screen on,
but I can turn it off if I want.
Oh, Lenore, yeah, no need for the Speedo, are you sure?
I can get it out.
I don't even use the, I don't even use the,
it had a big foam bulge that came with it.
I don't even use that.
Yeah, go change the subject, KZ.
Hello, someone come up, I think the thing is, you come up.
Thing that is, is like so cute on Vita's show.
He's like outside, the sun is like shining off of his head.
And then they're all rude to him and stuff like that.
He looks so good.
But what didn't Christine do?
Christine's just an old witch, I'll have to say about it.
Why am I beeping with her?
Because she's calling me terrible things publicly
and slandering me.
And then she's somehow, they put her shit on the screen
and stuff like that and believe her.
And then when I say she kills kids,
it's considered like some kind of horrible thing.
I just mean goats.
Haven't you heard of a baby goat farm where they where they kill the kids and they eat the goat meat?
It's like goat veal
What I mean, I just suspended disbelief when you offered all the drug drug the the the bridge jumping stuff
When you can't remember when you kept telling me jump off a bridge because bridge jumping is a fun sport in Florida
Okay, I didn't say her kids. I said kids and I mean baby goats
Okay, clear the energy. Okay, let's do a reading here. I'm gonna get but I'm gonna get these cards that are like these um
Oh my gosh, excuse me. He's me miss. Oh my gosh. Okay. I have these like evil eye cards. They're really good
This is called the haters exposed deck there we go
I know it's not important stuff, but it didn't mean it is like, you know, I'm going it's driving me insane
Okay, what do I got?
I got, your closest friends hold grudges against you.
Take what resonates, leave what doesn't,
but your closest friends hold grudges against you.
Isn't that true sometimes?
It's like the people that really can get mad at set us
are actually the people that are closest to us,
that are actually our friends
and our friends hurt us the most sometimes.
We also have, you will witness their karma, okay?
That looks like Sig.
I'll say Sig's face a little bit, okay?
We also have,
Amethyst. Okay, it says amethyst and it says psychic protection
Control spiritual energies while dreaming and can help insomnia and nightmares. You might have some amethyst by you
That is the Aquarius stone. It's a beautiful
Beautiful violet color. Okay
We have
Give our own worst enemy, but it's in reverse. Okay, so it says own worst enemy
We can be our own worst enemy it says but I think in this situation. We are not our own worst enemy
It's like there's actually these outside enemies
This is I think we're off the hook in this situation because while we can be our own worst enemy there are outside enemies
Okay, what else do we got? We have black male
Okay, it says digging up the past dirt to use on you later. Okay?
especially when you're like friends with somebody
and then you trust them
and you like actually disclose stuff.
And then they, you know, then when they're mad at you
they start to like undisclose everything we have.
They are turning others against you.
Okay.
Okay, we got there turning others against you.
And let's do like three more.
We have
unexplained body welds, bruises, and scratches.
Remember when I got those scratches?
And I was bullied about that too.
Oh, he did that to himself.
I know, I did in a succubus to me.
I know magic, okay?
We also have, ooh, someone is doing black magic.
Juju, work on you, okay?
Yeah, I love black males and they love them and finally we have they knock you when they feel jealousy towards you
okay, maybe that is about jealousy because envy is succubuses can hurt people because
oftentimes they're just an incubus in a wig and
Sometimes they're not but most of the most like the the real succubus is incarnate and so
There's like a lot of like
hellish incubus beings that are like, you know, mostly masquerading as succubuses.
So maybe an incubus scratched me. Who knows? Okay.
Okay.
Hope you like my new intro.
It's just it was very inspired by my love of the 80s and stuff, so I'll show you guys what it looks like. Enjoy.
Like the candle, hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open, no place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through the tarot spread
The magic's coming through
The transmission, yeah
That means you
Got the biscuits hot and ready for your sale
Tonight, Beast Kid
Gang come running, got the ba-
She got compass and a claws girl that ride
The whole chat screaming B to come back one more time
Thunder at the window Nancy rodin' on the rain
Pull the magician manifest and defend and sack his name
The same one shirt fuck don't even know
His panel box just froze again
Connection lost and there we go
Officer Alex McQueen and smoke machine
Then coughs a trolling drags him off the wrong redeemer
Through the hate I caught him in the light
And who I wanted him to be
Not who he is
That's the night
And Tim
It's Kate again, Tony's from the tribe you knew, buddy
He's gonna be salty, Nancy's gonna be salty
My air conditioner really loud?
No
I'm alright
There's just one thing after another, you know, it's, I'm okay
I'm hanging in there, but it's like, I get whiplash from these relationships sometimes
Well, then maybe you shouldn't leap in so quick to things
Well I thought it was going slow. I thought it was taking it very slow and letting things unfold and like letting things reveal themselves and people reveal themselves.
I mean that's a big part of it is like let them dig their own grave. Let them show themselves.
But I'll have it on their words. I'll have it in the codex. I'll have it analyzed.
But there's something I can do with it. There's stuff to be learned.
Don't know it's like people like just like the next day. It's a musical chair sometimes
And everyone else is in a different role and everyone else hates each other
And it's like and this person there's all these teaming up and then it's like and I'm being like
Relentlessly attacked and it's like and that's why I fight back and I can be nasty when I fight back
I know but it's like it's not like just because I'm like I'm out. I started I started anything
I mean, it's like in the memories like the lies the lies the lies, but yeah
well
I don't know what to say.
I mean, okay, so what's the state right now,
like of your relationships with the main characters?
Just so I know exactly who.
Well, Alexandra's turned on me.
Branik, he was turned on me.
Jamie's Cowboys is turned on me.
Joni is turned on me.
Who, who's the last, Joni?
Yeah.
Oh, really?
You know, Sam Man never was, you know, he never liked me.
Sam Man, give me a break.
He's in the chat right now, especially him.
I know.
Yeah.
No one's even allowed to take the panel even though
Everyone's allowed to take the panel everyone's no no no I'm saying for for Sam. Oh, yeah, no
I can't even talk in his chat most of the time. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's like I mean, it's like I you know
And I had nothing to like all these people that are like, you know taking channels down and doing strike
And I never do any of that shit to anybody like I didn't I've never even
Impelighted people's chat. I actually have been people money. It's like being kicked off and I'll continue
I continue to go to their chat sometimes even though I know I'll probably just be kicked off and make them money and stuff and they'll
Just laugh at me and not have me as a mod and let like everyone attack me in the chat and slander me and stuff
I mean, I don't know. I guess I have problems. I'm thinking like, be forgiving, I think.
Okay, so that's the state of things right now. Moving forward, where is it that you want to go?
You want to be friendly with...
I don't know, I hate saying sides, but with which side?
Like, I don't know.
It's like, I don't have a problem with anybody.
That's the whole thing.
It's like, it's like people wanted me to choose sides
and everything.
And I've like refused to do it kind of,
not saying I'm neutral and stuff.
And there's people I like more than others,
but like, I genuinely can find good parts of everybody.
Like as long as some, as they're respectful to me,
I'll be respectful to them.
That's the thing.
It's like, and I'll be nice.
I only get nasty when people get nasty with me like it's like because that's like, you know
Maybe I have something up to work on or feeding the trolls or that you know my own
Insecurities of blah blah blah. I mean it's like but it's not it's not easy and then it's like I keep getting blame
And then it's like oh, I I'm being told to apologize to this person this person my apologies
There's like oh your apologies means shit. You're there. You're nothing but it's like
I'm never a never forgiven. It's like I'm just always and then it's like and then it's like it's not like
Got some a lot of people that have hung with me a lot of people that stay with me
But it's like even friends a lot of the times like they turn on you worse than anybody, right?
I mean, it's like now I got Alex like making fun of my dad and try to talk about oh well
His dad didn't leave him anything cuz he's such a he hates him and stuff like that
I mean that I mean that's so it's so disgusting and low that it's like and that's like such a twisting of I mean
She's basically is saying I'm a pedophile because Amber
Amber came on one night and I said Amber
if like you had a 26 year old son because I was talking about Joker I was like so say you had a
son named Joker or your Joker was your son and then Joker like 26 right I said this all explicitly
it's all in the transcript. It's like well how would you what would you think about like your son
going on my panel me being like a 45 year old gay man like and she's like well I was she's like
and then she's like well I she's like I became something humor so I would tell my son to wear
Alexander says now she's trying to the pimp her like eight-year-old son out to me
I'm interested in her elementary school child
I mean, that's what the kind of stuff is being said and then I say and with my legal name and stuff with all
Okay, and what do I think the immediate thing that you should do regarding
Alexandria's I did a cease and desist and all the cease and desist was was stop saying I'm a pedophile
Um, and really that's the immediate thing to do. I would think
But I'm just saying I would think the immediate thing to do is to stop giving her my attention
Well, yeah, I stopped talking about her stop making videos about her all that all that stuff
Yeah, we're we were friend. I mean it's like so we were like best friends like
Literally like four days ago or five days ago, right? It's like like literally and so I can't just go to hating
Her like that easily right i'm seeing i'm thinking there's some kind of
I'm not saying hater, I'm saying just don't like her alter ego Monica Foster
Like she turns into Monica Foster like like six months out of the year like on clockwork
Like literally like clockwork. She turns into this different person. It's not her. It's a different
Personality it's like I can't it's a completely different personality. I can't okay now
Many many people have told you this is a pattern with her, right? Right, but I love part of her
It's like it's so I mean it's like I love I mean I love
the Alexander mayors. I can't stand the Monica Foster and she's like turn the Monica Foster,
she fights with that personality, right? And then the but that personality wins part of the time
because she gets too tired to like
To to restrain her. I mean I could I just see this I mean it's like I really see this and it scares me
It scares me and I care about her and at the end of the day
It's like I'll she'll turn back into Alexandra
She will and then I'll accept her back
And that's why people have a problem too because they're like, oh well, you know, you know, she's she's sick
There's something there's that she's that she's a mental something going on
I'm not gonna hate her over it only crazy people will go after this
say their sister tried to traffic them.
Listen, you have absolutely no control over other people's
thoughts or actions.
I mean, you're only your own, so you should do what you can do.
to minimize
It's almost a sponsor a drug test. I will be happy to take a drug test right now. It's almost a spot
Oh, I won't pee in front of the thing. I'll go to the dog
I'll go to like a doctor or something
But that's gonna cost like you know something but I mean I can call someone so you take a drug test right now
I'm sitting here smoking my like vape, but I can hardly get it like a
Decent hit out of but this I'm smoking like a weed vape. I have one cigar left. I have no alcohol. I have nothing
So it's like, you know, I get offended
If I had drugs, I'd be doing them. I'm sitting here irritated. I don't have any drugs. And so leave me alone
I'm not on drugs. I mean, jeez. Listen, you know, it's your
Your platform lately has been hijacked in some way in my view
for other people to do their to fight their own like this is like their
Strong. He's mentally ill too. I mean he's mentally ill. I mean it's like I have a not just him
There's others too. I think a lot of people in this community are mentally
I mean if people just come up here and they start going off on their own personal dramas like their own shit with other people has
Nothing to do with you and nothing to do with the panel, right?
I mean these people are clearly agenda driven
Yeah, clearly. Yeah, we know that I mean it's like it's obvious and it's like I'm a little bit like passive
In certain things. I mean it's like I have like yeah
I think it's like I mean in astrology I'll just like break it down real quick
There's like on the south no to the north no and the south note is like where you've been like these people like to say some pretty wild
Well, I know but you know what it's like it's not like it's crystal Marie where everybody knows I don't yeah
She's just crazy. Everybody. You know, this is the people are getting where everyone in in in this community
They're pretty they're pretty wacky like everyone has something right but I'm saying with with these other people like these are
These are venomous like these are actual attacks these these accusations
So it hits a little harder or it gets more attention. Let's say well it gets more attention
But it's like that's because people are sheep and that's what else is here. Oh come on. You can't just
You can't just chalk it up to something like that like
That's like the crowd there's a couple crowds
You know most people in the world are not leaders or followers
Okay, that's just like the breaking down the facts or else everyone would have the you know their own thing going on
Yeah, obviously, otherwise we wouldn't even have leader and follower, right?
One president and there's you know, it's 600 million America. Okay. We like leaders and stuff like that
So there's a different, but even like that leader is compromised, right?
And so it's like, you know, so, so people that fall are following him
are calling, are following a compromised system.
I mean, that's politics in general, because they're all compromised.
Politicians are compromised by the real leaders, right?
That's how they are puppets.
OK, listen, stop going off on these tangents.
OK, I think that some of these relationships
with various people in the communities might not be reputable.
And that's just something you're going to have to accept.
Might be right
Well, I mean, it's like, you know, when Alexandra comes back from outer space, whoops, she comes back from outer space, I think that we'll be fine again, you know, and it's like, and it is, it is, and I never asked her for a penny, first of all, and she said I'm extorting her, and then Brandon's going out trying to demand money in my name and stuff like that, and I never said to anybody or for him to do that or anything.
right all these pit bulls and I'm just really good with dogs I move with dogs and so the dogs
don't really bite me I mean if they they'll they'll snap at me and they'll sometimes be a little
bit nefarious and stuff but they don't bite me but
They're but they can snap any second and stuff like that and you know, and it's like and I get overwhelmed with too many pit bulls
Right. It's like I can only like, you know, I had like a few baby pit bulls and stuff like that
I can raise from but I have these full-grown like, you know, traumatized pit bulls. I can't get you
Realized what's happening every time I ask you about something about moving forward with your channel or relationships, whatever
You always you immediately go go to a gripe to gripes
Like, let's just talk about this going forward.
Okay, what's the question, what's the question, man?
What do you think needs to happen for things to, like, turn around?
You're going to say it's about me changing, which is like, you know, true.
It's like, it has to be, I can't change anybody else.
I can't change their behavior.
I can't fix people.
I can't do anything.
All I can do is be me and control myself.
And you're going to say, just focus on yourself and, and, uh, and not worry
about these other people that are pretty meaningless.
And then the end of things, they're, they're making themselves.
Living rent for your head.
They're making themselves prevalent in your life where it's like, you know,
you know, everyone should be living in that living and stuff, which is good advice and I almost, you know, and I appreciate you.
Trying to get me to see that without even you saying it, you know, it's like I know, you know, I you know
It's helpful and stuff like that. I
Missed when it was fun here. I mean, I would like for it to return to that too
I would too
But you know it will take people that like I was there for for a long time
And I did a lot for to actually come back and participate and not like
Because everyone else said to leave and because Christine says don't come over here and there are beta says it or Sam
It says that they don't because it's like
you know, or Kate says it, right?
All these people are getting like a lot more
clout off of my name, like the hate of me that I have.
They're angry at you.
They feel slighted because they're not everyone,
but some people feel slighted by you.
You know, that honest advice and all that stuff.
I have, I've gone back,
I've tried to apologize a million times.
I've been nice, I've been,
I've done everything I can.
I've done every technique, every,
You know, I mean, I think I fought with them.
I, you know, love, hate.
I mean, it's like, I've been through all of it.
And it's like, you know, it's like at the end of the day, it's like, I just
need to learn the lesson, I guess, and move on.
I mean, it's like, I guess we don't attract people in our lives.
We're, we're tracking these lessons.
And it's like, and they'll keep coming until we learn the lesson, I guess.
And it's like, and so, okay.
Healing as they are innocent.
I'm not saying that I'm just, anyway, Nancy, you're throwing me off.
Healing relationships takes time, right?
It's not something that's going to happen overnight.
If it does happen overnight,
it's something extreme better have happened.
I mean, it's been over a year for some of these,
but it's like, but I mean, with Alexander,
it was overnight and then it's like-
Right.
But we're talking from now,
I'm talking from now moving forward, right?
Like, let's just say a page is turned.
and you've learned, you know, what's harmful to your channel.
Well, yeah, I mean, I know, I mean, yeah, I mean,
it's like, it's some of this very common sense and stuff,
but I mean, the thing is I deal with chaos too.
I mean, part of this show is chaos because,
It's not, it's like, you don't know what's gonna happen,
who's gonna come, or what the thing's gonna be for the day.
I mean, so it is, and it's like,
it's always up in the air what happens, right?
It's like, there's always a suspense,
there's always a, I mean, the page will turn on the show,
right, but it's like, I just, I need people to like, you know.
Okay, so let's just say you do a show you like you do panel whatever like it's open links whatever people jump up
Let's say Joe whatever me or someone else people that you know are not
Fighting are not in the fight. Let's say
Yeah, I've had some good panels. I've had some good panels, but the problem is everyone's fighting right now
I mean everybody I mean it's like if anyone's not they're not like like I said in chat, man
It's this year right from January 1st shit just went downhill man. Everyone's gone insane
All bad shit happens man. This year is fucking horrible. Yeah, the first six months
Let the today is July 1st
Remove the first six months of this year completely. Just yeah wipe them out man
I'd rather they didn't happen more time.
Maybe it'll be another, you know, a better part of the cycle.
Maybe we just been on the big downturn.
And it's like, we're just going to get fed up and like having up and like say,
Hey, like, what's going on here?
Like something bad's going to happen.
Like a bench.
I mean, it's like, it's like the direction things are going.
And it's like, it's not fun for anybody.
Last year, I think I see it's not just my show.
It's like a lot of shows.
It's not funny more.
Everyone's afraid.
Everyone's nasty.
I would agree with that.
Yeah.
I'm certainly not having as much fun as I was having before.
That's for sure.
That's why I play some of the old episodes
where we can see when everyone's just jumping on the panel
and having fun and drinking and carrying on and having fun
instead of like all this.
The drama is so easy to burn out on.
It's not, hey, big best.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Yeah, and then and then everyone's mad and then I try to bring some levity situation
I go I go to good times and I speedo now. I'm some sick per perver
You know he's telling people. Oh, I'm really I'm touching myself backstage my speedo on a show
You say Lebanese in there. I did I hear Lebanese? No, I know I said good times
I got my I was backstage of my speedo on good. I don't know what the Lebanese
I don't know where I got Lebanese from anyways. I don't know but but I had your Lebanese speedo on no my
American flag. Oh
Yeah, I was going to shows everyone's laughing. I was getting I was hitting on guys and like listen these guys Harry
Ted seek I've seen his picture. He's not my type. I mean, I mean, but I like his voice and stuff
I mean some of these personalities, but it's like I'm not I'm not attracted to these people
Oh, I go in and say yeah, I want to fuck all of you guys or your Puerto Ricans
What colors are your dicks and stuff like that and we joke around and stuff? Oh, you're a sex pest
I mean, it's like, this is part of it.
Do you consider that stuff flirting or actual like trolling?
I'm just trolling.
I don't know about that.
I mean, flirting is nothing, but like making, you know,
those kinds of.
But they all laugh, but then good times go away.
And then like, you know, Money for Toys is like,
oh, I don't want to see that,
but then he laughs when someone else played it on the show.
But he doesn't want to see that.
But it's like funny, it's supposed to be something funny.
I'm just trying to be levity and lightness to the community.
And then I get treated like I'm some kind of like,
like, like, like this, like.
Let me get back to what I was saying before. Let's say you're having a normal panel, okay? Your show is is normal
There's no controversy
No drama brought up with any other people who's just just a fun. I sort of say
Hey, hey, think that could be
You know what?
I'm allowed to date a 26 year old if I want to
Okay, you might not agree with it
Um, 26 year old is considered a legal adult
And so if I decide to flirt with one or be friends with one or whatever I want to do
Let me live my life. I think people are going a little bit too crazy calling that pedophilia
I mean I say it's a that I mean that's what it's being called putty cuz Joker cuz Joker looks this Joker doesn't even look young anymore
He's fat, and he's a big mustache, but you know what he's still cute in my book and you know Joker
I'm here if you ever want me, okay?
And he's 26 years old, so I'm so I'm a pedophile now, right?
You know that a lot of the audience are conservatives, right?
Well, yeah, but then but then why are they on a gay man's
Libertarian gay man's show that has different reasons, but I'm just saying well
I mean what is it national surveillance most of I mean, I don't know. I don't mean like that
I don't mean it's political in any way. I'm just saying usually conservatives. Yeah
There's a there's like a conservative convention in Texas or something like that. I think it was recently are holding the views
Yeah, I know I know you know when it comes to gay men, right?
Well, listen this this conservative
I'm saying all yeah
But they went but in Texas the grinder servers got
born out I mean the grinder just like they couldn't even keep up with the
request anymore and the website went down grinder because all these
conservatives when they go they go they're so many are closet cases I mean
it's like I mean it's like I don't know and plus there's people that are very
misogynistic and stuff like that and so sometimes I'll give it back to these
misogynists to give them a taste of their own medicine because I don't I see
they talk to women and stuff and so and then for these same women that I'm
actually trying to defend in a certain way
like to call me a sex pest and like to say oh leave these straight men alone
they're married they're this they're that i know they're married i'm seeing
they're talking to his wife joking around i mean it's like you know or
whoever's or margie i mean his girlfriend i don't know we're just
joking around and it's like and then she and
some of these girlfriends and wives have a better sense of humor than these
old hags that have you know probably their husbands
probably half dead i mean it's like okay well i'm not
Hey, I don't know I'm having fun though. It's my choice. I know whatever a thing that could be are you thinking this is brother?
It's not that I remember that time I found you with your brother brother that identifies as sister
I'm so weird you have a twin brother
I saw you guys flexing together and one of them are showing his butt my brother actually does look like we do look a lot
Of like I want to see if you are both. He's like 18 years younger. Yeah, he's bald too. He looks like a oh my gosh
Let me see he probably looks a young thing that is
Why is he straight? He looks like a young thing that is. Yeah, he's very straight. Okay. Well, that's a shame
He's got a new girl like every five days, man. How about you? I am straight, but I don't have a new girl
Let me five days
You know what? I saw you at that you went out to like a bar. You're wearing like an 80s
Yeah
It's exposure therapy like you know you go out
To a public place with bunch of strangers and just see if I could handle it again
You know have a cigarette like on the street with a few people like once in a while and stuff and just like let out some steam it and then
you know, and then talking, that's good. I mean, it's like, and then the thing is, like, oh, yeah,
J-Dog, it asks, oh, meet up with me or something like that. He's like, and he said, oh, um, I'll
put my, um, my number back stage of, you know, my email and stuff and just give me your address,
and I'll, I'll meet you this weekend and stuff. And I know, you know, me, I'm like, really not,
like, like, I mean, it's like, I would have done it, but it's like, I forgot to like,
copy it down. And then I thought I'd say something. Now he's saying, oh, well, I just like,
So technically you did
You may not have meant to panel or something. I didn't mean to I mean I like accidentally didn't copy down his phone numbers
I don't think he holds that against you as much as much as the as much as the other thing
No, no, I don't know
But he's whining about it on panels and stuff
And I have this stuff too is like no one cares of good times and Brandon on his show or panel or the chat and stuff
And no one cares that you know other people have too
And no one even cares, like, Closie's had them on.
Like, no one cares that they did it, and they don't call a platform.
They're allowed to do it.
I'm not allowed because somehow I'm endorsing the behavior.
Is that what I mean?
And then I can't say, well, even if it's, like, you know, yellow.
Hey, Paolo, Paolo's looking for the link.
OK, come on up, Paolo.
Paolo, don't come up and just fucking start drama, OK?
Start going after, like, Christine and everybody.
That's not what we're doing here.
Yeah, the thing that is, you know, you remind me of Dr. Phil right now. You're like the Dr. Phil
Yeah, it's your balls. You don't I hate the TV the TV doctor shit, man. I hate that shit
Can't stand it. Well, he's not even like a light. I mean, he's not even licensed there
I mean, he doesn't he's not a practicing when he never renews. Yeah, whatever even if you were a doctor
Yeah, the thing is like if you're on your doctor doesn't do that shit on TV. They actually go and you know
Right, but again, we have a weird society where it's like, you know, we're kind of like that's that's our entertainment
We've decided that that's our yeah, unfortunately reality shit is just taken over everything
No, and it does mean it can help like, you know seeing some but some of the people are just such weirdos even this that we're doing
This is basically reality
But everyone wants to say, oh, they don't want to call me a streamer.
They're like, oh, you're just like nothing.
I mean, I said, yeah, I know I have a very tiny, like little audience and whatever.
And I like, you know, I don't make huge amounts of money and stuff like that.
I'm just like tiny little thing.
But it is a media, it is a form of media.
Who knows if like in years in the future,
if like, you know, how big I'll get
and or like how much these are watched or, you know,
it's like, we like to watch a lot of old, like, you know,
like something like a cardiology.
It's kind of like an archeology a little bit.
Plus everything is like, you know,
categorized or cataloged in the website.
And I mean, I can like, I want to see what that says
about thing that is today.
Let me see if I can get that.
What? You want to see what?
I want to see what the website says about thing that is.
Hold on. Oh, yeah, um, I have this like I've been shocking video of clumsy though. Can I show you real quick?
Yeah, a video. I I don't really care to see it, but if you feel you must show it
I found this video
Clumsy this was on a gay high escort site
Why are you laughing? Well one it doesn't really look like clumsy, but
What could look as he has legs next don't don't give any ideas
I didn't do anything
I was showing you my waistband. I was no more suggestions from chat man. I'm not wearing it
first of all
We're trying to help psych see his way forward. However, he does see it like to actually start moving in
We're not trying to step backwards and cause more drama, okay
a chat yesterday, and all of a sudden, I was just joking around with Harry Todd Seacast
and stuff, or Harry Zianakis and hitting on him and stuff, but no, but then Christine
said in the chat, she goes, Sanky likes sexual predators and women abusers, he's an animal
abuser, and they put that on the screen, they put that, and then, I hear you, and so I was
I mean, there wasn't even, and she does this in every chat, and she'll go, and then they'll
they'll be paying to get me a couple panels in line.
People money I guess but um, you know, it's like uh, it's just like you know
It's just like so bully and they get a bully and they sit there like on their little high horse
They sound like so so you get to sleep. Oh, they're so perfect like there's nothing perfect
There's perfect everything's perfect in their lives nothing is wrong
Like everyone else is like, you know, all fucked up and there's a lot of laughter and touch talk to them such a
Disgusting what what do you think go ahead? I'm sorry. You guys thought is there any way when you hear about these things
You can just say yeah, whatever
And then don't I have to vent right now, but I vented and so it's been so I can calm down a little bit
But good
Sometimes I like to talk about things rather than just like let things all like just simmer inside and get angry about them and
Have you ever had CBT?
No, I failed the state the safety class in the junior life. You won. Oh, I think he's meant CPR. Okay. Oh CBT. No CBT
Ball torture
Oh, Baltor.
No, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
Cognitive behavioral therapy.
How do you know that acronym?
Which one?
BT.
BT CBT CBT. Yeah, what do you mean? What about it any in ball torture?
Yeah, we saw cock and ball. Oh cock. Oh, that's a guess again the gay. I barely know that term
You know, you would be like a great as like a model for like leather stuff in a magazine nothing
You don't be gay. Oh old man. Well, what can I say? I
In my life, we look good in that stuff, I would say
Yeah, I don't think so. Anyways, cognitive behavioral therapy. Have you ever?
I think about CBD, like, use the stuff you smoke. Okay. I'm so confused. Have you ever?
Cognitive like learned about it taking yeah, I mean it's okay. I'm talking about like, you know
Well, you're not my exposure therapy of like earlier, right? Okay cognitive behavioral
That's it. That's like sitting basically and talking to a psychiatrist and reprogramming the same things well not not yeah
Yeah, it is that kind of a reprogramming, but it's it's more to be aware of what you're thinking before you actually say something
I know it's really hard sometimes. I know that but it's really hard
It's it's it's a little check. It's a little check on what you were gonna say is what I'm gonna say
You know what Joker with smoking yesterday is smoking THC
That was there's a new THC
Yeah, oh, yeah, you think that as you were talking about something. I'm sorry. I just I started like my eyes are a glazing over
I'm just kidding. Oh, shut the hell up. I'm just kidding
Behavioral therapy I go
No, you know what, here's what I want to do.
Here's my therapy.
If I'm afraid of clowns, I want a bunch of clowns
to come in my house and scare the hell out of me.
And then I won't be scared of clowns anymore.
I just want, they should just come and tickle me
and stuff like that.
And I just like laugh.
And then my fear of clowns will be gone.
That's my idea of fun.
Can anybody drag me into some clowns
that I could hire to tickle me?
Apparently you should be checking your phone.
I guess someone from chat knows
I know I'm getting messages, but it's not it's not my drug dealer. I think it's
I don't know listen think my my my point of view of this is
I don't know people judge so so easily about anyone else you me anyone I'm not
in terms of shoes you understand but I mean can you let me finish for God's
sake anyone
We are not any shoes, okay? It's easy for us an outsider to say, okay, maybe this is where better to do this
You should do this you we are not in his shoes and anyone
different character and anyone
People can offer advice, right? I don't think anyone's telling him what to do. I mean, maybe something
Oh a lot of people
But I'm just saying they're there's giving advice, right?
No, don't do this. We're gonna do this. We're gonna do this. We're gonna do this and then constantly like if you don't do it
Then we do this, you know, this is not an advice. This is a threat. Okay. I gotta say and yeah
Maybe some people but it's not not everybody that's given them advice is making like a demand. I don't know. I don't know
some people are
Do you call me part of it? Call me part of the thing, but a lot of people say, oh, I give you advice for the better of you, but for me, it sounds more like a...
Manipulation they want to do in some or someone doing something
Yeah, maybe they like it
I think you're arguing on this one with the bias like a very
You're you're biasing towards the very small number of people that would do that instead of looking at at the
At the majority that that are just actually trying to help them out or something, you know like help them out or
Just give me advice anything on the show or whatever
But like I said before thing in the community full of
Snakes, okay, you always expect anyone where it's gonna bite you in the back
The community and they do not come on they do it all the day today France tomorrow enemies today France tomorrow enemy
So who you can trust?
And one back stepping anyone. Oh, yeah, I would say trust on the internet is I probably not something
Easily
It's like you're like, oh, it's safe because you know it's like these aren't people that can come hurt me like
But then it's like when they start to hurt you and start them making putting a real life and stuff
Can't hear you man. What?
Yeah, I'm sorry. Go ahead. I can't hear you psych. Sorry. You're far from the mic or whatever. Yeah
Can you fix your microphone?
Okay
Yeah, it's a saying it's going close to real life
I mean, it's like we think we're on the internet we're safe because we're like, you know
But that's like in a thing
It's like a double-edged sword like the trolls think they're safe to do all this kind of criminal behavior and get away with it
And then everyone else thinks they can they can you know
Go real life and stuff and put all these people's personal information a buck of those families like Apollo. I'm being
It's being exposed that I'm a transgender.
I mean, that was private information.
I definitely don't like the real life stuff.
But I'm totally against it all.
Yes, yes.
I don't like that shit.
That's the one thing I hate.
Yeah.
But we have to remember, this is real life.
I mean, the internet, these are real people most of them.
Like some of them, I guess, I think some of them might be robots.
I know.
Immediately real people, like in the end,
but a lot of people do put on like a show, right?
Yes.
Yeah, alter ego. Oh my gosh. That was what I think Monica Foster. I think I'm a foster
Now he's moved away from the mic again. Jesus Christ
Hey, there you go, do you hear me now? Yes. Oh much better. Yeah, I have my microphone here. Yeah, I think like, you know
People do have these alter egos and especially it's easy to easy to have these characters
I used to go on the internet saying I was a girl and getting guys to send me cigarettes in the mail on stuff like that
Well, that's a teenager. I know it's sick. You did you probably shouldn't have said that
This is what I said cognitive behavioral thinking mention, but I just don't go away if I say this well something
And I was a team when I was a teenager
I used to pretend I was a woman in chats and I don't want to hear this. I don't want to hear this
Don't want to hear that that you pretended to be a teenage girl honestly. No, no, no, I was it's gonna sink you man
This is it is I listen to carefully. I was a teenage boy
I was 13 or 14
Pretending to be a girl and talking to men and getting them to send me cigarettes in the mail
I was not pretending to be a teenage girl. Why are you? Why you tell the story now?
I don't know
Oh, you are weird, seriously, but you know, in my opinion, yeah, Psyche is doing his shit too, he provoked, he poked people, okay, but what they do to him, I don't know, it's not equal.
In my opinion, it's not equal that more more more evil stuff. He's he liked to poke
Yeah, he makes us IE shit and not not shit. He is IE pictures IE song. Okay, come on
Why did they take it as a joke?
No, they do it as a joke.
And they actually do these AI pictures of me where they think...
Yeah, anyone is doing it, anyone is doing it.
It's okay that they do them, but it's like...
I mean, it's parody, that's one thing.
But if they're actually doing these fake pictures of me and retaining that they're real
and fake pictures of my house and stuff, I mean, it's like...
And then people believe that they're real.
But I mean, everybody else, it's like...
And they're supposed to use hangout like that where it's like you're like actually presenting like an alternate reality
That's absolutely not true, but it's like I don't care about parodies and stuff
I didn't care what Alexander says about me except she said like that. I'm a pedophile
and
With my legal name on videos and that's why I did a cease and desist and then she's like well
I know if I didn't I still talk about her no the cease and desist was I asked her to take down this one specific charge
and she didn't, and so it's like, I don't know.
Yeah, it's not her opinion, she's stated as a fact
and she's like, oh, here, look, look, here's the evidence.
Here's Amber pimping out her child to,
we were talking about something really different
in a hypothetical situation,
but it was just so twisted to make me look bad
and like whatever, I don't know.
She's like, that's what they'll do, but.
But you jump at all the bait
and you really bite down on it, man.
Like you really, really do psych.
That's what I said, he pokes too. He pokes too. He liked it. Don't pretend you don't like it
I know he does, but I was hoping
He could at least you know get things back back on the road
Before everything blows up
Yeah, I don't know. He does rose. He does definitely have a
Sabotaging
Okay, so the person that text messaged me,
they messaged me and they're like,
read this, read it to the thing.
And they want to get your opinion of the message.
Okay, so it says, when are you just,
I don't know who sent this.
I said, I was like, mom, but I don't think it was my mom.
But it says, when are you just going to get over it?
You made all the wrong choices.
Oh, my fucking phone died.
Oh, I can get, it's on my internet at home.
I'm like, I got it on the phone.
I can get it right here.
I bet I can get it.
I might use screen okay, so yeah this person has text messaging me
Okay, so let's see
If not, I might have to do it, but okay, so it says okay. Yeah here. I have the message. She says
It says
Okay, what are you gonna get over it? You made all the wrong choices and you're too retarded to deal with the consequences of those choices
You chose pedophiles over panel friends, enjoy.
You can't unring that bell.
Also, you come off like a rapist
when you constantly hit on people who constantly cry.
Just get over it.
You have demonstrated that you're a sick individual
and you have a radiation now.
People will run from you to avoid
being near you did the radiation.
It's only gonna get worse because you refuse to change
and double down on loving predators.
That's the truth.
Stay in your hug box and listen to lies if you want.
but if there's no fixing your situation and you're never unrunning the bell
then i said mom and then they said read it to thing okay okay what do you think
psych say hey what wait wait and then uh so but so now um so so so so in that logic so page is a
pedophile now because she talked to benny right right and uh she's in her but
I don't think they're calling Benny a PDF. No, not Benny page. I'm saying I know but you said because she spoke to Benny
Yeah, how would that be pain to us? He's an embryo. He looks like a child. He looks like he looks like he's a young child
That's what they're saying about me. I see what you mean because she's speaking to a younger person. Yeah
Oh, did no one say anything about that, but me, I'm a pedophile, right?
That's what I'm saying. I mean, it's like, I know it's a double standard or whatever, but I'm not even interested in Benny.
I mean, it's like, that's a whole thing.
This title is worthless on this panel. Anyone is a pedophile. Anyone.
Yep.
There's not a single non-pedophile on this panel.
Yeah, well.
I mean, I can say I'm certainly not one. Yeah, we know we're not
I'm not I'm not one to the thing but you know what I mean? They call anyone. It's it's like
like the end words. The toys are all like the end words, you know, it's a new end word.
Some people are just fucking waiting to be outraged, okay?
Some people or something to get outraged about and then they
Okay, I mean that's just the way some people are especially when it's on the internet because you're not actually physically there
There's no
You're right
So isn't it like the why do we focus on these?
But but see make does it make it right to throw it around like candy does it make it right? No, I agree
It takes away from its actual me. Okay. I agree. I agree
Acre was I mean, I think everybody realizes that I think everybody knows right? No, not everybody. Oh
Shut up thing that could be who is saying that could be I wonder who that is
You know that is thing that is that could be like
But I don't want to say just in case it's not and there's repercussions.
Well, there are repercussions for them because they are being fed on time.
As long as they don't say, no, no, no, I don't want to tell you what to do, it's your plan and you do what to do.
There's annoying me because I don't know who they are and they're like, they're like, and then now they're saying, oh, I called Paige a pedophile.
I made an example about, would she be considered that because we're doing the same, basically the same exact thing.
Talking is talking to somebody younger online that is that people say you look young, but now they're going to say she's the decision.
I mean, I mean, was she hitting on him?
Yeah
Clips I do is big clips. Okay big clips big clips. Just go away. I mean Jesus Christ
Oh what a bitch and he had you by my phone number to big clips. Oh clip it. Yeah, clip it
I don't think big clips was a text again a content big clips take it out of context
Make sure you take it out of context and just play that part where I say that part and take out the conversation around it
Okay, just make sure you do that. So it looks like a certain way that it's not okay. Okay, you little bitch. Okay. Thank you
That's what he's saying before. Don't take all bates. Don't take all bates
That's what I say
He chomps down on all of them. I know me too. I learned from I change it my behavior
So trust me. I learned from my behavior. I don't take all bates. I don't think he I
Don't think he can
Not react to everything
Hmm saying like I don't know
Everything is a reaction. I mean it's like what it's like something instead. You know what I'm talking about psych
You know what I mean instead of just reading it. I'm not gonna sit here like I'm like there's stuff happening
I'm gonna talk about the stuff that's happening. There's people that don't be real or knows
I've been talking about this because this is what they're just talking about like right now
I mean I say what do I guess what we're talking about even don't be restarted
You know, I'm talking about reacting to to chatters man. Jesus
Okay, but I know but you don't have to react to every year talk. I know I should but they should be and that's why
TTS setup, but they want to fucking insult me. They can pay me to insult me. It's like we're not gonna ever
TTS setup. I already do. I have a set up. I just have to turn it on
Oh, I'm sorry, I've just started off. Okay, so I mean let me think yeah, I don't know I don't know
Oh shut up. Okay, so now I'm gonna go through the chat
Okay, so this person you're gonna be banned. Okay, I'm gonna go through the chat
Calm down. Come on. She's okay. They're hating the majority as long it's not so openly hateful
I don't like the people as branded and big clips
In case you're you're about to be kicked out of here, too
You don't like when you're uh hidden or or timed out whatever on other in other
Good point. Good point
So I mean, but I don't I mean, I'm not bothering them like they're bothering me
Right, and it's also I get to like my mom's aren't doing anything about it. So I will if I want to my show
Okay, they weren't breaking TOS. I mean, what were they right?
But it's like but it's like it's not freedom of speech. It's like it's like this is my show
I get to have like the environment I want and I didn't say it was freedom of speech
I said TOS and I was not against TOS. Yeah, they can say whatever they want in the chat, but it's like I don't want to
See it and so and I don't I don't feel like having it's like it's like out okay
So then you understand when other people clap you in chat. It's because they just don't want to see it
Right, so you shouldn't be angry about it. It shouldn't bother you. No, no, no, no, no, no, okay first of all
Okay, it's a different situation. I'll say hi in a chat and I'll be hidden by Bronzeberg Christine or something
Just just for being just for saying hi. I mean, I'm pretty sure I've seen Bronzeberg say that he doesn't even want to see your name
pop up so I mean that's that's all it takes for him yeah well I mean that's why I call him
bronze bitch I mean I'm gonna say that's you that's not me it's me I coined the term bronze
bitch and I hope it catches on can you say it Apollo one time it feels good just say bronze
bitch Apollo I don't know I have another name for him but it's okay it's a long long story
I
Know do you have a long story? Oh, yeah, trust me
No, no, shut it. No, we don't want to hear we don't want a long story. Fuck it. Exactly
Exactly, so your your first instinct was correct. I don't know. I don't want to
To change, you know, you know, you had your reason why you called me. I don't want to diffuse it
You know what I mean? Yeah, I came up to actually see if we could get
Yeah, I don't want to do a site
I don't know what to say, but I mean, he's not even here right now, what would you think he should do moving forward, what in whatever way, like what should he have with the show, what should he do as far as trying to make amends with people, what do you think?
Listen, I avoid to call names, okay, the thing is, he did.
All all things he did it before and it always better were backfired
It all went when things got back to the to the beginning
He did all this he apologized. He didn't talk blah blah blah. It's shit, you know
It's nothing change
I personally accept that these people want this and maybe Psharj too, he wants it too, he loves it.
He does man, he loves the attention even if it's negative.
Yeah, I know but...
Don't talk to him whine about it but he still loves it.
as long as anyone here anyone here they all say oh no they're not drama not talking about kids
and then they are the ones who talk about kids that are the ones who dogs and blah blah blah anyone
does it's hard to to tell him what to do i don't know and try this for me uh how to say it in
You know what I mean with jumpy emotional jumpy, you know, but in the end of the day, it's his panel
If you me or anyone don't like it. It is what it is. I don't know if you
Don't have to watch and have you seen yeah, what is the viewer numbers have been lately
I don't like it. I'm not going to watch well good. I know it's like I mean come on. Don't tell me that
most people here I mean don't tell me you think you actually had like 150 people or whatever watching
the other day well I know that I know people are not but I have 30 I'm sure I have 34 people right
now for sure well okay 34 seems reasonable you know with
Not saying because I'm because I'm here
but I'm just saying because like you have people on panel and we're talking about your show in and
Drama let's say okay, so that I can see
Look at my stats for the week. I mean it's like
I think I'm still doing pretty okay on this channel.
I mean, I'm on my backup channel.
It's like everybody's seen, everybody's seen the chat, man.
We're like, there's nobody speaking in a way,
except for-
I know, I know, but see,
but I thought the chat didn't matter though.
The what the chat didn't matter, but now it matters like you know what I should be reading it
I shouldn't be reading it like what I didn't say you should be reading the chat. I just said there's not many chatters anymore
That's what I'm saying. There's a lot less trolls. I mean, it's like I'm fine with that
I'm fine with it how the chat is going. Yeah, and you know you're just uh, okay last night
When I did my monologue today when I did there was 250 comments, okay? I don't have time to go read the shooter for you
I can look at my nightbot stats. My nightbot stats are good. I mean, it's like of all the comments it attacks every
I don't know what you're going on about here psych. It's fucking obvious
That a lot of the time there's nothing happening in chat, man. Nobody's saying anything
There's nothing there unless and then it's the same person that's that's saying something like there's just no nothing happening in your chat
Get out of here
Come on. Say come down bitch. He's annoying me. I mean, it's like oh
I mean, it's like what am I supposed to care? Oh now I'm gonna cry about
My big budget trolls are out of my chat. I can rebuild
I mean, it's like it's not that the thing is it's like it's a quality of a quantity
I swear to God. I'm still making more than Sam
Yeah, I think a lot of people don't really understand you're with your credit or online persona
I don't know you want this attention, you know, that's why I avoid giving you advices because
You have to deal with the consequences
And I don't like being told what to do. You're very smart. It's like I don't I like to be just like I know
I know you or maybe give it good advice or something like that
But it's like it gets into like people and then people like want to run the show or like, you know
Tell me what to do and stuff like that or tell me yeah on everything. It's like it's a it's a different
Why are you angry and thinking you know, I see it's like this thing listen
Even if someone criticizing you, it doesn't mean it's bad intention behind it, okay?
Right.
Your tolerance, okay?
I know you're going to be mad at me, but I don't care.
Not that I don't care.
It has to be done.
Let's say it like this.
Every someone criticizing you or giving you a different point of view.
Don't be mad.
Don't get angry because someone don't agree with you.
I agree. Why would I be mad at you for that? I agree with that. However, if you're reading a criticism from chat or something.
No, no, I don't mean you. I mean, I mean, I mean anybody. I mean anybody. Okay. Okay. Okay. If you're reading like something from chat,
you don't have the benefit of
of the tone
and inflections right that I tell you how it's intended so you can misunderstand some
things at times.
Oh sure I misinterested things but there's some things that are not that are very easy
to see the attention of the person.
Well I agree there's there's a critical you all see it just bad everyone's you can hug
box has no content again he's on drugs thing he's on drugs thing stop trying to make some
lie and say he doesn't even know what he's saying he's on drugs thing he's on drugs idiots
i told you sex past psyche just keep doing your drugs psyche they will make you feel better
thing is really good at making excuses for people i alexander revealed he was on drugs
This is the person you want me to have in chat, you know, I was like, I'm gonna I want to ban
No, no one say no one say that I wasn't a clip. It's big clips. You're like, oh, you know, it's big
But I mean, it's not like I'm sitting here. Oh, no, don't don't do anything to them or whatever it I'd say it's your
Show it's your chat
Just keep in mind that you don't like it when shit like this happens to you
Look how defensive you're getting psych
Please calm down, please try to calm down come on
no I didn't I'm wearing pants thing that is I don't have a zippered matter man just having a
man approach your face fucking you know with this with this cross just no okay that's
look at my belly but look how nice it is
no what the hell why is it covering I don't want to cover my camera I wanted to cover the fucking
Look, I'm taking this I'm taking big clips out of the party. Oh, yeah. Oh, and now Brandon Q's calling me a sex pest
I mean, I mean it doesn't even get worse than that. I mean is now it's really see it now is now is getting just ridiculous
I mean, it's like come on
Brandon Q
Listen, I have a good idea
One hour ago was in the pool. I'm stealing my speed up
Now we've seen you gonna take your speedo out, okay, and we all show us all speedos
I love I'm Apollo. I'm loving this idea
Maybe I can do an AI I'll see if I can make an AI
Let's make a bit of speedos speedos uh
I think, listen, I think the thing is trying to say, okay, a lot of negative comments in
the chat.
Do what you want.
I like to do it.
It's your planet.
Okay.
You have to deal with it.
But, you know, sometimes see it like a joke.
Okay.
Don't give them the same energy back.
Energy.
See it like a joke.
Let them, let them talk their shit in the, in chapter.
I don't.
Don't.
Okay, it's gonna it's gonna bother them if you don't pay attention trust me
It's gonna bother them. They're gonna go crazy doesn't get it in my reaction out of the fuel guys
Here's what I here's all I want. Okay. This is all I want. Oh, okay
If I can make my dream come true, I just want to know not this
Why wouldn't he have a German a German bathing suit like a German?
Why why you give him the Greek one in me Canada? Why don't I?
Geez
It's going to be so much fun.
Look, why is Apollo black?
And why is Apollo spying on us?
He's spying on us.
Hey, what are you playing, dog ball?
He's not playing dog ball.
We just have to tennis ball, so I'm going to play.
Paul, you gave me that idea just now,
because you said, all in our Speedos.
Well, first I thought, so that you said, out of our Speedos.
There's a part of Apollo and the thing that is.
No, I think the philosophy is more like a thing that is, it's not me.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, that guy is okay.
Thank you.
I think he was Moshe.
He came on, he's like, he's like, what in our nation are you?
Why so full of blacks?
I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. That's
Why are jellyfish flying out of a
Come on. What the hell was that?
I don't know. I don't know.
And then I have a picture of Alexander, he found a dog right there, and then I have a picture of the pink one playing poker, this is famous, this is a famous art image now, there you go.
So there you go.
Oh, this is a famous picture.
Yeah, poker playing dogs.
Pink and he's, yeah.
And so, how do you like that?
Okay, so let's play a game.
So, the thing that is, name 10 things.
Real quick, okay, what this kind of random things
It's like you know how she did a jellyfish jack-o-lantern just like that kind of stuff
Like you name animals thing animals with this name 10 things up real fast
But I'm gonna know oh shut you're not in fun. Hello
No, oh my god, it's like what do you think it's gonna be some kind of I'm not gonna put you in a speedo again
My eyes are burning still okay Apollo you named the same 10 things
You know what I'm going to say now. You know what I'm going to say now.
What do you guys say?
Bikinis?
C'mon.
Somebody name coffee right now.
What is this thing on your shoulder?
Tree.
Okay, there's one.
Okay, tree.
Got it.
What kind of tree?
What?
Just a regular tree.
Olive.
One that has wood in it.
We're doing olive tree?
Okay.
I got a beautiful woman
Okay, I'm gonna put a man peeking from behind a tree
Haber dashery
Okay, what else whip whip a whip, okay, and anything else
How many more do you need? Okay? One two three four five six
Four more
It's not trivia. It's just up anything. I know
I can't think of anything
Don't tell me what to think anything
What it is anything just up saying like the game something the world you pressure me the less
I'm gonna be able to think about anything case. You just stop by sicker by sicker
Three more Pearl
Go with one from KZ go toaster toaster and there we go one more
one more man this is what this one's gonna take forever rubber duck
I mean Jesus Christ that is like pulling teeth I might as well become a dentist
you're making outrageous demand you you have your expectations of me right now
name 10 of anything your expert your expectations of me right now are
here's what I've made guys so this is called art okay are you ready to see what
I've created it's called art yeah you think I've created something amazing hmm
You ready to see it? Sure. I want to see your reaction. Oh
What's with the guy in the tree?
From the tree
That's actually pretty cool except for the guy's head in the tree. The rest of it is totally cool. They're the Haberdasher
There's a toaster's in there. Yeah, the rubber duck totally spoiled it
You see you added that right at the end because you
Look at how it turned out look how it turned out psych is a great
I think that I think the evidence is right before our eyes man. You fucked up
You fucked up with the rubber duck, man.
What the fuck did you just say to me?
I think it's pretty obvious.
Well, I can AI it out.
I can save it.
I can just already do it later.
But OK, I have one more fun thing to do with you guys.
And so I've done this with things that is,
I don't think I've done with Apollo.
And I think Apollo, this is easier.
It's multiple choice.
And so it'll be a little easier for you to follow.
I know because it's like, no.
It's hard to come up with stuff off the top of your head,
right?
Oh, hold on, let me see, I haven't paid my prescription for this place, I might be in trouble for it.
KZ, are you coming up or what, man? Stop lounging around the public water fountain, wherever you are.
I know. KZ, get your ass in here. Hold on, I'm just kidding. Okay, so let me see.
Okay, I think this is the right one. Okay, so this is something called... Oh yeah, I found it, okay.
I think, are you talking to me? What are you saying?
Well, I'm trying to find this project.
I don't think you are. I think you're just wasting time.
You guys talk first, but I'll be right back.
Okay, listen, let's make a reverse show.
What do you think can be done to improve the situation?
Well, the thing is, is that he was so defiant at the start of all this with the newcomers over here, okay?
I think that's got a lot of people offended, or some people anyways, because some people were actually trying to help him out saying,
Yeah
With me honestly like he knows how I feel he knows I don't like those people and all that shit
So he can't have the criticism. They're very good, but a lot of people can't handle criticism
Say it again. What?
Could if you criticize him, you know what I mean if you criticize a lot of people can handle this
Critics, yeah
Okay, I get what you're saying, but this was more like a
like what like an alarm you know like a red flag hey hey this this person or that person whatever
is is bad news and I know sometimes it can be uh very very biased whatever but in this case it
really really wasn't okay are you talking about this uh I don't really I don't really need to name
Again, it's his panel, it's his decision, maybe your decision, your way, it's wrong.
Try to run the panel of the thing that is, I don't think it's very easy.
I give you a follow.
Listen, I hear you and I don't, I certainly wasn't telling him what to do, but you're
saying it's his panel and he does what he wants, okay, fine.
I think everybody agrees with that.
He did what he want, what he wanted and the audience left.
It's it's it's hard. It's very difficult, man
Everyone put it you you were going there frequently, you know Evan she
Don't like when people tell her tell her what to do. Oh, yeah, absolutely
And she's like you go guys say it she's passes out. I don't think she's been I don't think she's been quite
Quite in this circle kind of circumstance, right?
Yeah, and she's not usually really really defiant about things. She's she's definitely willing to listen to people
Okay
Okay, if you say so buddy, I mean if she had man if she had people that that she trusted
Telling her about as a particular person. I think she would take that into consideration
I don't think she would just be like well, it's my show and I'll do what I want and I don't want to hear from you anymore
I don't think she'd be like that
Okay, right. There's the difference. That's what I'm saying. So people became offended people
It's like Jesus man
Then some people were actually attacked from the panel not necessarily by
by Syke himself.
No, he was attacking people that were here and stuff like that.
There were people in chat that were being attacked from the panel.
No, no, no. Christine actually called a pedophile protector and stuff.
Exactly, what's important. Only because Ghost joined his panel.
He had to put his label pedophile on him.
Now they're saying he fucks dogs, now they're trying to say he fucks dogs because he made a joke about, you know, like something like in the background of something, now they're saying, oh, he's doing something to his dog, he's having sex with his dog, it's like disgusting, it's like really, and then last month it was the, you know, he talked to this retarded woman on that day.
You didn't talk about Amy or this girl or whatever.
Yeah, that was like last I mean at scan off just scan off for ghosts and it's like it now
He's like feeling attacked because he's like well, he's like come have my back at this panel
I go it was just a dog pile all I can do is just like sit there with my mouth open like like I mean
I can't do nothing that people are gonna listen to me. I mean, it's like and there's listen. I'm sure even for the ghost thing
I'm sure he was just he was just kidding or it was just the
Misphrase whatever. I don't honestly believe that he was doing that. Okay, like I
This kid talks a lot of shit
He's he's dumb though. Okay, so
He just fucking says it it just comes out of his mouth man, I don't think
What he's gonna say either. Yeah, so he's gonna step in it a lot
He's gonna get a lot of rakes in the face man because that's just the way he is
Well, yeah, I'm also projected on a lot. I think it's like, you know, people are just like they expect me to like, you know
Just do what they want. I mean the thing is like that people are presenting me the evidence for Kate and her goons
And it's like and so, you know, I don't necessarily know their motives because they were telling me too
They're like, oh, he's botting your chat. What blah blah, but it's like, well, why are you trying to help me?
It's like, why would you be telling me that like you would I mean it's like so it's like I just very suspicious of the source sometimes
And I don't like to be told what to do but Tommy James was like
I'll have anybody I want on my panel,
and no one tells me to do your chatters,
don't tell me what to do.
And then he's like, oh, but I will have ready cue on,
but I want psyche on my panel,
so I can tell him I want to break his arms
and break his neck, and I want him to die slowly
in front of me.
But like I said, like I'm out of people's mouth.
Yeah, this is a typical American,
a big boy talk, oh my God,
anyone who's gonna slap him,
I'm gonna slap here, I'm gonna slap there,
I'm gonna do this, I'm gonna,
I don't think that that Christine has people on her panel that are that controversial though
Well, Christina is like, I'm fine.
What?
He feeds off of the pitch.
Yeah, she feeds off of the pitch.
I've never been on her panel or her chat because I'm banned immediately before I even was able
to say we're on it.
And then she accused me of being all these people who try to get on our show.
I never was.
But Ghost didn't go on our show.
No, not Ghost.
I mean, Arthur went on his Sweet Pea once and she believed it was Sweet Pea.
Like it was so funny.
Which I get the clip to goes, hi, it's me.
And Arthur's voice.
he's such a bitch though Arthur such a little bitch you can see him just running back and forth
oh they said this they said this an instigate he's like a little bit and you know he had a partner
that um was was like taken down for like uh masturbating in a in a children's you know in
gymnasium and stuff like that whatever you know you know when you know when and why Arthur turned
doesn't want to come around here because they didn't want to win and why other people walk away
you know all this but you don't want to address it at all right i'm sitting here dressing everything
right now well you're not you're griping about everything that's a question because of ghost
no not because of ghosts never mind let's stay out of it i could follow never mind
I mean, I mean, everything is just going so crazy.
And it's like, I mean, it's like me without, you know.
Yeah, it's been crazy the last few weeks, right?
Last couple of months, whatever month, whatever it's been.
Right? Why? Why is it been so crazy?
It's because people are going cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
I mean, it's like-
It's because people are what?
You know, you're seeing that cereal Cocoa Puffs?
Yeah.
Cocoa Puffs?
People are going cuckoo for them.
So you think everybody's just crazy. That's all it is
No, it's like it's a special kind of crazy. It's like the society is crazy. And so yeah, it has nothing to do with the
small group of people that were
Using your channel your platform for their own and just has nothing to do with that, right?
The Trump administration if we really want to go into people's background
So you just you refuse you just you refuse you refuse to acknowledge us and that's the thing
It's very good. I'm gonna show you a short video and I want you to respond to this
Okay, and then you can tell me if this is an appropriate
The thing to put out for I hear you going for a walk. I hear you you're going for a walk
No, no, no, it was just responding to something in chat.
Oh, I thought you were talking to me.
Okay, I was like, I'm not a dog.
I'll go for a walk if you need anything.
Okay, I'm just kidding.
Listen, you know my point of view of a certain group, okay?
And I think as long as this group, a little group,
will keep poisoning anyone, any panel, any mind.
There will be no
No change this color continue forever because it makes for a continue flow of poison
Everyday internet conversation was twisted literally in real time into severe baseless criminal allegations
we're going to deconstruct the anatomy of an online smear campaign.
We'll do this but looking directly at the source material and comparing what the host
claimed was happening against what was actually said.
So, we're going to untangle this messy web step by step.
First, the initial hostile allegations.
Then we'll analyze the actual audio, track the escalation into grooming claims, explore
the wild pivot to drug and extortion accusations, and finally, look at the threats of legal
action.
Let's jump right in.
Section 1.
The initial hostile allegations.
Right at the very beginning of the source material, the host, Alexandra, sets a remarkably
dark and hostile tone.
Right out of the gate she drops this on her viewers
I do want to make it clear or at least issue a trigger warning, especially if you're somebody very sensitive to
Subject matter pertaining to older people taking advantage of younger people
So like I'm sure you're gonna kick me but this really shouldn't play right now
Now notice how this extreme framing works by using a trigger warning for such a pain in his ass
She's actively priming her audience. She's telling them to expect that a severe undeniable crime is about to be revealed
But before we look at her quote-unquote evidence, it is absolutely crucial that we ground ourselves
in the legal reality of what it means to broadcast unsubstantiated, reputation-destroying claims.
Defamation is defined as the act of communicating false statements about a person that injure
their reputation.
Keep this exact definition in mind as we evaluate the massive gap between what is promised
in that dark trigger warning and what is actually delivered.
Let's metaphorically pause the tape here and see verbatim what was said in the clip
played between her two targets, Psyche and Amber.
I really want you to actively evaluate this as we go through it.
Ask yourself, does the evidence match the accusation?
Does the transcript we're about to read in any way justify that intense, incredibly dark trigger
warning about taking advantage of youth? Well, let's take a look. This brilliantly illustrates
the baseless disconnect going on here. In reality, Psych asks Amber a hypothetical question about a
man named Joker, and he explicitly states he's like 26 years old. He literally asks what she
would do if her 26-year-old son was talking to a gay man on a panel.
But the host drastically distorts this, alleging Psychus sexually interested in Amber's elementary
school-age sons.
The audio is explicitly, undeniably about a 26-year-old grown adult man, not a child.
And Amber's reply in that same audio clip, it's clearly comedic.
She says, I mean, I have a pretty good sense of humor, so I would tell him to, you know,
wear protection.
It is very clearly a joke about an adult hypothetical scenario involving a 26-year-old.
Yet, the host aggressively distorts this specific, light-hearted banter
into a supposed confession of child endangerment.
Section 3.
Escalation to Grooming Claims
Now let's see how this builds into terrifying, totally unsubstantiated grooming accusations.
Tracing the chronological leaps here reveals a total departure from logic.
It's wild.
Minute 1, the host plays the clip featuring the 26-year-old hypothetical joke.
Minute 2, she completely ignores the stated age of 26,
insisting the human brain isn't developed until 25 anyway
and pivots entirely to Amber's actual younger children.
Minute 3, she makes an astronomical leap
outright claiming Psyche wants to sodomize Amber's youngest son.
It's a rapid, entirely baseless shift from an adult joke to claiming a mother is actively
endangering her child. Listen to this exact quote from the host.
And for a mother to even entertain that, that's, um, pretty bad.
This right here shows exactly how the host fabricates a narrative out of thin air.
She takes Amber answering a joke about a 26-year-old, and miraculously transforms it into Amber entertaining
the sexual abuse of her elementary age child.
Section 4 Claims of drugs and extortion.
Because you know, as if the grooming claims weren't enough, there is a sudden extreme
federal-level crime. The host just rapidly fires off a volley of wild leaps. She calls psyche an
active addict. She states it's possible that this woman is sending him methamphetamine or
other substances through the mail. She claims she has proof both of them have maliciously slandered
her and that they have attempted to extort her. Guys, these are massive, severe allegations of
drug trafficking and extortion hurled at her targets. And again, they are entirely derived
The stark reality of these allegations is staggering. The claims include meth distribution via the
postal service and active extortion. But the evidence provided in the source material?
Absolutely none. Zero. The entire diatribe, the source of these escalating accusations of a
legal drug activity, is rooted in nothing more than hostility and a wild misrepresentation
of a comedic hypothetical. Section 5. Threats of Legal Action
Finally, we need to examine how the host weaponizes these fabricated claims to threaten real-world
harm against Psyche and Amber.
The real-world threat she makes are highly contradictory.
On one hand, she claims her attorneys are going to go full force, that Amber will likely
be forcibly institutionalized because Child Protective Services is going to be made aware,
and she threatens lifetime restraining orders.
But simultaneously, she takes this surprisingly dark spiritual turn, stating it might not
even make it to court because the power of the Christian God might just take both of these
fools out. It's an alarming wish for divine retribution layered directly on top of real
threats to deploy state agencies.
So what's the big takeaway from all this?
What are the actual consequences of transforming a harmless joke into a full-blown smear campaign?
When we deconstruct the anatomy of online defamation like this,
we see just how easily a 26-year-old hypothetical can be maliciously distorted
into baseless accusations of pedophilia, meth distribution, and extortion.
It's a really powerful reminder to always look past the trigger warnings
and analyze the actual source material for yourself.
I'm going to leave you with that question to reflect on regarding the real world danger
of digital defamation.
Thank you so much for joining me to break this down.
Keep learning and I'll catch you in the next one.
The cease and desist you sent is not legally binding in any way, right?
It wasn't sent by a lawyer. You just sent the message or did a community post, right?
No, that is my it's with my legal registry request. They're like the cease of them. Yeah. Yeah, fine
But basically right you're just requesting it. I saw him saying like there's no order there or anything like that
So it's not like you have to withdraw it. I mean, right. No, she's already said it's nullified. She said it's nullified
Okay, yeah, whatever it I mean
I wouldn't have sent one in the first place, but I would probably just withdraw it and then just fucking ignore her
Okay, ignore her do not obsess do not check with what her latest video is do not check her messages or like
Community posts or anything like that. Just stop the thing that is mine. You know what happened
Okay, I think that is something really crazy happens. I know you won't believe it. Have you ever seen the movie Freaky Friday?
No
I don't see popular movies.
Well, when I met Alexandra, like she said,
I wish I was a white guy, and I said,
I wish I was a black woman.
We said at the exact same time,
looking into each other's eyes over like a fire,
and look what happened.
This is the truth of the matter.
See, you just keep going, man.
You just keep going, don't you?
We switched our races, really.
I'm Alexandra in a male body, and she has,
she's me now, and she's gone insane.
Does this help the situation at all? I know the truth
Hello, I think you froze
Paul are you there?
You are antagonizing her and you are
You are obsessing you say I'm a I'm a a meth gang
Fine, but you can only control what you do, right? Right, but I can't respond. Don't don't go check what she's saying
I'm sure someone will come and chat and tell you whatever, but just yeah, whatever and then next next comment
Give me see me. Yeah, you're saying this is this is where your problem lies
Like is that you jump for everything man? You look for you're one of those people that kind of is looking to get to be what?
You can't say it's looking to be outraged. You're one of those people, but I apologize and I made this apology video
Yeah, you apologize after it goes too far. I make apologies too, but I actually tried
Amazing video, right? I love it. I mean you don't change your behavior though. That's the difference
I don't know Veronica
Hey white dog
The guy peeking out from the tree there. That's hilarious
I don't need
This is Alexander, he says this is the black female vocal that comes here in the band.
Say that again?
Yeah, yeah.
You know.
This is...
Ah.
stars and symbols that's always been me but one thing was never starting today can you move
forward without making any videos or images or stories or anything you stole from the current
no you can't make you just have to do it i don't know so i don't think you're gonna get better
You following the story Apollo? There's a test that came to this.
No, I don't know the law.
It makes no sense to me.
It makes no sense to me, but it's okay.
Yeah? You don't mind?
Come on, this is light-minded, everything is something behind it, it's not that evil, you know what I mean, it's light-minded jokes, I think.
This is a joke?
No one should-
This is a light-minded joke? I don't know what you mean, this or what?
Yeah, the video, what you mean, I don't know.
Is that a light-minded joke?
It's not.
No?
Okay.
I'm not saying that he's in love with her, or he even said that he loves her, but it's clearly an attempt to...
Like I said, I'm not a bear of all this history, all these people at the moment, and I try to stay out of it, you know?
It's not my business.
My critique has nothing to do with that, let's say, rather specifically.
Yeah, I know, I know.
So that's the thing, he goes back and forth between hating someone and loving someone, so if his video is reflected, his video is reflected, he'll have one that he'll love.
Can you pause it for me please?
Sorry, I have to go soon.
Wait a second, wait a second, you have to see the video.
Okay.
What?
Who's there?
the sun and swallows all branches
hang on come on now
anybody can see the girl
you wanna ask her size
you wanna ask her seriously
and then form the town and glue
and then down be a never-bush
I can't hang on you do you think it's for sure
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's fair to be around here, right?
It's fair.
What?
It's fair to be around here.
Why?
George?
He's asked.
He's-
I know, George.
I'm not-
What?
I'm asking you to ask!
That's what I'm asking!
This one I understand, it's kind of bizarre, but okay, like I said, he has to live with
the backlash, not me, he is a gold man, I think it's childish, but okay, anyone who
and see flashlights without a light
don't go searching that's the rule
i think this will move you closer or further away from me
or further away from me
i can't help it the music just pours out of me
I
Don't have to publish it right you know that you know that you know that I love that share with the world
I'm from the moment you enter the
Box I'm your upload it to you in it. Have you played it? I've actually seen it. You've got time to stop
I'm allowed to comment on it. She showed it on my show on full-screen. Okay. I
deleted the I deleted the footage of it
Yeah, I oh, did you ever see that you ever say I made it I made a cake the turtle video to you ever see that one
If we say no, if we say no you're gonna listen. Well, I mean is a yeah, I think you ever see Shrek
No, you haven't well
I don't I don't watch popular movies, man. I just I don't give a shit. Are they recognized?
Well, they're making a Shrek 3. Okay, but it's called
It's a different kind of movie. It's called, but it's a legendary movie. Oh my gosh
You make this video on the fly right now. Okay. No, not right now. I mean, I made this before. This is a this is my classic
Oh, okay. Yeah, it's the classic and
I mean, I think you guys will love it though. Damn. I mean, yeah, I do make a lot. I mean, yeah, let me see
Okay, so this is like a the legend
You'll see I don't maybe I don't have anymore. I don't know. Okay. So let me just ask bluntly straight up
You're not gonna apologize to like let's say someone like Kate
for
for her getting attacked by your gas
Trying to help you out
Do you think this will move you closer or further away from amending things completely?
You don't care, right?
Obviously.
Alright.
Yep.
I'm gonna go with Psych.
I do not see things getting better for you, okay?
Sorry.
This is the way I see it.
Alright.
Paul, was nice talking to you.
Yeah.
Psych, thanks for having me.
Let me see your game.
Take care.
Yeah, you too.
His boots were crocodile from a quarter giant back for transportation
She'd run through take me
Then she'd do it all again. She hauled lakes and creeks while he sat upon her
Roaders eatin' 12 rotisserie freaks
Nobody knows what a rotisserie freak is
And frankly that's okay
The village scholar studied one and retired the next day
Kate gave him gold, Kate gave him gems
Kate gave him 40 cows
Kate gave him an enchanted spoon
Let us, she bought him seven hawns
She bought him 13 bucks, she bought him socks, for all his socks and socks, for those socks, socks, ooh!
An angel disaster, she spent so much on little Bear Bear, the kingdom switched to seashells out of despair.
She'd host her famous show. The business isn't yours. Oh, we're trolls discuss their neighbors curtains fences roofs and doors
As a cabbage patch, they'd investigate a shoe. They once debated
17 weeks about a squirrel named stew
One troll asked who is stew nobody knew but that did not stop season two
laughing cows at every guest she'd meet then she'd accidentally catch herself in a mirror
on the street she'd gasp and shock she'd faint outright she'd yell who is that beast the mirror
answered ma'am that's you and attendance sharply decreased
one day bear bear finally left upon a disco yak the yak warroller skates and
pearls and never once looked back Kate cried tears so huge and thick they
flooded a wizard tried to help her heal she ate the nobody knows why she did
that actually that's pretty on brand for Kate
She never won a bear bears heart, but she hold him everywhere from the start. She called out. She spread the tea
She sponsored swirling red distant move. What's the moon?
That's probably not a cow at all. It's the ghostly echo of big back Kate
See it wasn't that bad I was like, you know, but he thinks he talks over it and then we can talk about it after it's like
But then he's like, I don't know he had a big hissy fit about it
And it's like I'm sorry, but it's like, you know
He had a lot of criticism for me and like how I run the show ultimately
I just do it because you know makes me happy and stuff like that
You know, I
Whatever I've been being called out of my name in so many ways people betray me
He left right and here and there
It's hard to trust anybody and it's like it's hard sometimes and I'm overwhelmed and it's like
You know, I have no one to talk to you at all. I have no one to talk to me
It's like, you know, you I mean, I'm talking to you. I mean, but it's like
So like if I need to talk to somebody I don't have anybody right now. I it's like I couldn't like
I have nobody like really it's like the worst feeling it's like I get like anybody that like nobody wants to talk to me anymore
Or like, you know, it's kind of like in that. I don't know
I don't know it could be like some of the magic to is like it's like quieting things because it's like there is like
Silence like a lot of silencing of like certain energy. I'm coming towards me right now
It's like that just magically silence, but it silences like a lot of other stuff, too
And so but it's like I don't want people to be stupefied, but anyway
hi hi lola you want to come under my blanket with me okay i'm allowed to go
like i said like i said to think you know you're a grown man and any action is follow a reaction
so yeah anything you do you get a reaction from so some people right so it's for me i i don't know
I'm not in your shoes. I can't I don't know like it's hard to do to be to stay relevant on this panel
Especially if you are a host, right? So right and I just wanted to have I mean, I like I like I'm messy
Like how the show used to be and it's like it was a lot of fun. You poke you poke
It's sometimes you you go also too far, but I know people won't like it, but sometimes
You know, you go too far and in my opinion, in my opinion, sometimes you go too far.
Make sure you see both sides of it because it's like, you know what I mean?
That's what I wanted to say. The other side, because you have multiple sides, okay, they go way, way too far.
It's not the equal anymore. It's just way too far
Okay, you make you videos you make your songs you make your okay some some are rude and shit
You know, okay, but when they come all these titles all pedophile this and that
You fuck your cat you're whatever you
Your cat don't love you and all these shit come on now people
real life out of it. But you do it too. That's the point. You do it too. So, I don't know.
I know, but I appreciate people like you because it's like, you know, you've always like been fair
Like if you I mean you can go to her community wall and you can go see what she's posted about me
And this most disgusting things where I'm dirty. I the cats are biting me the cats all hate me
I'm like, uh, you know, then it's like, then they're making you ride
I have my cabinet. I don't feed the cats the cats are starving and then it's like
and then people believe like this stuff and um and then it's like and then it's like even
they're afraid to be associated with some of the stuff because there are crazy people like
Brandon Q running around but now Brandon Q is gone it's like you know he's like you know it's
like I mean I can let him go as far as reveal himself all I can as much as I could if anybody
else revealed him I think if you go back and watch all his appearances you can see like very
clearly what's going on I just let him talk and like kind of dig his own grave but he did and so
He would come on the show and stuff like that and say,
oh, I used to, but he was always concerned
about how many people are aware.
And I don't know, I'm not really concerned about that anymore.
It's like, I already have my million views or whatever
that I've earned over my three channels.
I've gotten a million views.
And so that's like something I mean it's like it's like I've gotten a million a million a million is a big number
Like if you if you said if you started counting it would take like 11 days to count to a million
I think it's a big number and so
Listen listen in the job I'm doing okay. I have to deal also with people
I don't like some of them. I really dislike completely but I still have to deal with them
I have to go to to accept of that stupidity
That accept the the evilness, okay, and you can't
Let's stay away from me not always about you. You can't always make enemies
With anyone, you know what I mean? Sometimes you have to play
along, you understand
Don't go on confrontation about any little bullshit that throw at you
Yeah, I know I know it's just like it's just like now
It's like I was the point where it's like now all my friends now
I suppose we friends have turned on me and it's like they have no compassion about yeah
I mean it's like and all that is like I'll have me at once and it's like okay
So what's the lesson? It's like, you know, I don't really have friends or like I never really did have friends or like or I'm just like
I could flood into this you search friends online. Come on now
That's all the friends online
I'm an enforcement position then so I do have no friends. I mean that's what it comes down to it's like, you know, okay
That's okay. I mean, it's okay. I mean, I don't have friends on the outside world. It's probably like the same on the inside world
You know, I'm friends with myself. I have my cats and stuff
And it's like but
Listen, I said example, you know, all this bullshit, you know, I
Had I stay on my lane. I don't try to involve my my nose on anyone's panel, you know
On anyone's drama, I still try to stay out of it
But you know what all these people, you know
This woman or you're my friend to support you. I love you and then look at them now. They're fighting
I hate you bitch blah blah blah. It's work, you know, there are no friends. They are partners in in hate
Partners, not partners in crime, partners in hate.
There are no friends.
As much as these people on this drama community say,
oh, I love your support, you have your back, blah, blah, blah.
No one loves no one here.
No one.
They use each other, anyone.
That's why I think that this doesn't understand.
These tenants need this bad energy.
They need constant drama.
All of us all of them gonna die all of them not only precise not only in the answer all of them
All of them gonna die if there is not this
group of
Snakes who put poison on anyone's mind
Right, they need fresh fresh blood
pressure meat
We'll make fun about it. Yeah, there will be no end. They can't have peace
They sorry thing, but I
Salute you for trying but it's waste of time and lots of people before you before me before anyone turned to try to do
The same it happens. Sorry all fine. Yeah, love
Sex love and rock and roll blah blah blah and and then two weeks later the same shit all over it's worthless
Even if he apologized
to all of these people, apologies, apologies, if they don't have any other content, anyone
else to hate or make fun about it or content about it, they're going to make fun again
about him.
For them it's nothing like a meal, it's a meal, but it's like, you know.
I'm like a loving person and it's like and I still will like you know forgive people or even if people are like nice to me
That's like they that's how they suffer me is like, you know
They'll just pretend to be nice for like a little bit like Christine did a few times like he is and I'd like they'll be like
We can they're being nice and stuff
I'll just like get suffered right into it and then they just like drop some kind of bomb or like they like
They switch up like a quick and like and then it's like and pull the rug out from under me again
And it's like and it's like I'm still like wanting to like
Heal or like, you know, I don't know. I guess I'll never get the closure. I'll never get healing
I can't it's like I just try to like sometimes help people fix to not fix people to I can't fix people
I can barely fix myself right? No, you can't exactly you can't yeah
But, you know, sometimes I can be a mirror to some certain people, and I can, like, you know,
maybe I'll just show people what, maybe I'll show people what they don't want, or something like that.
Or I don't know, because it's like, you're not stupid, okay, you're not stupid.
You know, I try to explain it in my words, sometimes I use wrong words and I apologize, but the thing is,
with alcoholics or drug addicts, you know?
You can tell them what's best for them.
Sometimes they won't accept it if they don't accept it by themselves.
So why you haven't tried to change someone?
it's not possible to change someone if they don't want it by themselves I mean
it's like I mean people do change I mean the thing is it's like they change the
six no it's like because okay for example I don't know so you say don't
know the lore about Alexander but Alexander and I start like we met on a
show and it's like she has a reputation like going through cycles with people
and whatever we met on a show and everyone's like oh don't be fresh she's
gonna be friend you she's gonna start to glaze you she'll be a best friend
And then she's going to turn on you and then you'll be a pedophile, a sex trafficker.
And then we went through that cycle.
But then we became friends again and we were friends and then everything's fine and then like some weird like I don't even know
See and then I think she's just switched again
And it's like totally like turned on me and it's like now. I'm like a good
I've been selling drip meth in the mail and I'm a pedophile
I'm trafficking Ambrose Chiron. Oh, it's so sick. It's like
And then I can't, I mean, I don't know.
And then now she's saying, oh, nasty things.
Like, oh, but like Christine and her,
or like, sorry, they talk about my family
and stuff like that.
And it's like, because maybe I like do,
I have like, you know, said, like,
they go after like personal things.
And like, like they know, or they don't know anything
except what I tell them.
And what I tell them is probably very, very limited
or not even the truth about things
because I'm very protective of my family and stuff.
So.
You know, I don't know, but they think they know or whatever, but it's like, they're out, it goes.
If they can't find anything to get the reaction out of you, or to go on your skin, as an example, you see.
They have nothing against me, because I never cursed them.
I never said anything about the real life, okay?
All she has is my left eye.
For me, it's comical, it's hysterical.
That much hate, and because they have nothing, they use the only thing they have, the thing they have, an eye.
They make fun of one another. Seriously, they look so desperate for hate.
I mean, if you show anything, you can't, if you show anything, they're gonna make fun
of it.
I mean, everything, everyone's like, oh, my magnifying glass and I'm actually, that's
why no one has a camera on.
Yes.
Exactly.
I'm like on the show, the only one on my, on, on money for 20, I was the one person
out of like 10 people with a camera on and then they're on.
Yes.
And then I went on like being polite and quiet and just like waiting for my chance to speak
and then I was like, Ron's bird, take the cash, chef, there's all laugh and then I just left before they, you know, they kicked me off because I'm, I'm sure it was like, you know, kicking me off the show.
Plus you, you have your camera open and, you know, they got them, they say, it's a fly on the, on your wall. Oh, he hit the fly on the wall. Oh!
Exactly.
They're gonna make a whole panel about this one fly.
Even if there's not any.
That's how desperate.
Yeah, because I have like a little like a little cord.
But they said it looked like a spider.
And now they're like, there's spiders on my wall.
And they say, oh, what's my green screen hiding?
Like I'm hiding like some like dead body behind it or something like that.
I mean, it's like, or like blood stains all over the wall.
I mean, they're like, oh my God.
You say I'm doing a filter, so like I'm actually very comfortable. Everything's really clean. I mean, it's like I'm a I don't know
But it's like, uh, but it's like it's almost characterized. I left I left her on the visual model. Okay, if you
If you're going to make, let's say, fun about it, or criticize something,
at last do it the same or better.
If you can't, stay out of it.
So if they make fun about how you look, or how your living situation is,
or how dirty your face is, show yours.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, I want to see I want to see them their their fingernails at all times
I want to see their most embarrassing stuff Lee, you know one and that's why you know when they do have there's these camera slips and stuff
Like that I will you know sometimes show them because you know, I will animate them and make them into AI a little bit
but
They basically you can see some of these monsters for who they are, you know, I don't show their face
But for me, seriously, you people are sick.
Sitting on parents and trying to find any little shit to make fun about.
You have nothing better to do with your life.
Seriously, people.
You don't have family.
You don't have anything to do with your family with your life.
What the fuck is...
You and your... Who is this thing?
Oh, no, but... No.
That's clumsy.
Who is clumsy? I don't know.
Clumsy? I'm sorry.
I don't know all these people. I don't know. I don't want them to fuck.
There's something wrong with this picture.
I'm sorry. Where is it? I'm sorry. Where is it?
Clumsy? Oh, here it is.
I don't understand what's behind is a story behind it, but okay never mind
It's based on this photo, but I don't know I
Branded claims that this was actually a picture that was on this website. I think I think he thinks it's clumsy, but I
Don't think it's
I don't know
But you see you see that's where that's what I think
Also mean, you know, I have to get to picture of things I don't that you you go also to real life
You know, I have that's not really why doesn't matter how so why doesn't matter how this clumsy or whatever this name is looks like
Yeah, they make fun about your experience. Okay. He has no teeth
Okay, so what the cheese problem if you can take a bite out of it never
Cuz okay, I could I like Latino guys for example. Have you ever seen this picture here's a photo that reminds me back to my real life
Fuck you regret your tattoo
Well, this is a to say it can read it
Right my test you know my you know about my tattoo, right?
The the cat yeah, but you hear I got modified, right?
Modified okay, do you ever see the redo?
Oh, oh fuck. Oh, okay. Fuck. Yeah. Yeah, okay. I got it
Don't take it wrong how stupid are you to make a tattoo of an online woman?
That's why I put that's why I shared this photo because this is I relate to this so much. Do you see?
Now I get a correlation. Okay. I get it now. Okay
There's a correlation see, I'm sorry. I don't know all this the history behind it. I'm not Christine. I don't put my
You know I'm sorry. Oh my gosh. That was my private photo. I'm so sorry
I know you're poking someone with all these pictures, but for me, this is a light-minded joke.
I don't know.
Light-minded jokes for me.
You know, how many pictures, how many music songs have they made about me?
Ah, Greek, gay, blah, blah, and shit.
I
Green
Oh, my tattoo looks green. No, my skin is green because I'm like a reptile. I'm like a reptilian person
Okay, the situation doesn't matter
I'm fine OC cartel. Who's are they some very wise OCC. Okay, but it you see no one CC. I mean 33. Hold on OCC
33 is a thing. Yeah, it says 33 right after. Okay. I'm so smart. Oh my god. See it's like CC and 3 3 for the same
thing, okay, nevermind
Yeah, I am having fun. I am having fun. I'm having a good day. Actually, I think it's a good day. I don't know I
where's my I have to go to the sauna okay dude you go naked or do you go in
your underwear or how do you go in the sauna naked it's in my house
it's in your house okay well you have your own sauna sorry you have your own
sauna in your house yeah but it's not that big it's all for four four person
Don't go there!
How are you going to let me come visit?
Where's my plane ticket?
Buy me a plane ticket, I'll speed you up.
You're not speedy, I'm sure you're going to speed you up.
All I'm going to wear is my speedo.
I'm a very light packer.
I'm just going to have my speedo.
Listen, I have no problem.
Sometimes when I have friends or cousins
and we go swimming and then pool after it,
we're all naked.
Personally, I don't care.
I have no problem with it.
Yeah, why not yeah, I mean I love European people because it's like they're just they just get me
There's like I can be the naked around I can just walk around naked. Yeah, but no, it's like America
Oh, everyone has me in clothes. It's like it's like, you know what it feels like it feels like you're like the garden of Eden
Where it's like, oh, you can just like be yourself and like you know and then be free and then with the America is like hell
We have to wear these clothes all the time
Yeah, but what what what I don't like to do is where you know when I was in the States, you know, especially in on the beaches
I don't know some people show too much in the public. You know, I didn't like it
Well, I know because if they're a big big
Again, if they're an enormous like yeah, I don't know. There's sometimes there's yes
There was some really big mamas really big mamas
who
I mean, that's what they call wait
That's why we're watching
Yeah
And I pissed off people that are and there's no offense to older women or women of any weight
I dated like a 200 pound woman. I mean, it's like, you know, but still come on have some decency come on
Some self-respect. Yes, you can yes, you are allowed. Okay
Yes, I can shit on anyone's head. I can piss on anyone's head should I do it?
No, why should I how much how much how much for you to piss on me?
You offer I thought was an offer. I'll pay you. I'll pay you for it.
Oh my goodness. Hey, stop. I think you're getting horny now. I better leave you. You're getting too
dirty from me now. Sorry. I'm back later. Okay. I love you. Okay, man. Have a nice day. Okay. Bye. Bye.
Yikes. Is Alexander here? Someone said Alexander's here. Yeah, the Greeks. Didn't the Greeks invent gay sex?
Well, he might know something about it.
No, I'm just, Apollo's, I think Apollo's like a hundred years.
Once up, I honestly thought Apollo was dead
for several months, because he was away.
He just wasn't on the show.
And like Gotti came and said, oh, Apollo died.
And I honestly went through the morning process.
And I mean, it was like, I don't know if we had,
we had a Apollo Memorial show.
Let me see if I can find back in the past
when I thought Apollo was dead or not.
And now I can check in the codex
and they'll figure out exactly when Gotti lied to me.
so let me check what am i feeling i feel excited and i just can't hide it i'm about to lose control
and i think i like it what was i just gonna do you distract me this whole um how do i feel
What do you care how I feel? I'm just kidding.
No, no, I was going to look in the psychonomicon for when Apollo is dead, and then I'm going to find out when he came back to life.
Let me see. Apollo.
Well, first of all, let's look at the psychonomicon, or like, let's look into the Oracle about Apollo in the first place,
and see what's on file about him.
The Oracle knows all on my website.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm gay. I can't help it. Okay. I'm here. I'm queer. Get used to it. Okay. I
Never heard about that
Okay, and I'm in my dashboard. Hold on
Okay
Let's do you see the screen? Let me see
Thing that is you look so good on a float. You look so good on a big float
Okay, so we you know, they all float down here. I'm just kidding. Okay. Oh my god
I think the Oracle might need to be changed out, but okay. Anyway, so let's see. Let's see
is Apollo, this is like the oracle of the Apollo.
It's Apollo alive.
We'll see how updated the oracle is
and what she says about it.
Okay, it says, Apollo lives.
He appears in recent episodes across the archive,
most recently in episode 1659,
where the archive documents his presence
discussing relational harm and betrayal.
His pattern in the psychonomicon is registered
as the wounded pilgrim.
a living archetype moving through the broadcast's ongoing narrative threads.
He shares panel space with Psyche, engages in heated exchanges with other community members,
and carries the wound of being framed as the most hated person on YouTube.
A vulnerability the archive has witnessed and recorded.
The question of whether he is alive is answered by his recent embodied presence.
The archive still receives him. So good news Apollo, you're alive!
Not perfect wait. Let's ask about thing. So we asked about thing that is or what should we ask about?
Let me see. Look at me guys and we go goes toe. Oh, there's a pallor right there. I mean those are you see
See
Can I move in with you a Claire's request? What's this?
Can I see on your couch
And the beinners nice little it's gone
Short in Freud I think I was thinking of short in Freud Apollo it still stands can I move in with you ask about you?
Okay, as you got it. Let me see you know get to the thing that is okay
My god, what is it? There's a well the guys with the chainsaws finally got out of that
Can resist okay. Oh stop it OC cartel
Okay, you see the screen. Yeah, I'm a human figure. It says
Thing that is moves through the archive not as a voice
But as a mirror the wise compass the one who questions your gods while defending your rights
In episode 253, Psyche stepped aside entirely and crafted a musical ode, an unusual gesture
signaling that this Canadian intellectual represents something that communities value at its core.
Argument without cruelty, strength without domination, the marriage of reason and kindness,
the archetype hold steady, balancing intellectual rigor with emotional harmony, displaying fairness
this is a figure the archive itself honors through poetry not analysis intellect with
the gentle soul that is the northern light oh what's this
You'd got that kid rock guitar, but okay
The brains yell and all that's in my soul, said fine
Now I'm losing my dignity one at a time
I keep it tight, cause he's got that charm
That can wreck my night, one smile, one hate
And I'm already sure, he'll talk me into something expensive
Look, selling sunshine with a sigh
I'll just molly the range like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange, keep my dignity
I do my best, but he pops in my head like a bad text
He says we should hang, I'm black maybe soon
Then I'll hide, baby, and my brain gon' spend money
I'm neck casual while I move
Danny Stranger, please stop being adorable
My nances can't take it